{"uploads": {"u-e094e3f1": {"id": "u-e094e3f1", "name": "icdc.pdf", "description": "100 questions.", "questions": [{"id": "u-e094e3f1-q1", "number": 1, "question": "For a contract to be legally binding, it needs to outline the benefit that both parties receive, such as money, services, or anything of value. This describes what key element of a legally binding contract?", "options": ["Legality", "Consideration", "Capacity", "Offer and acceptance"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Consideration. For a contract to be legally binding, it needs to include several key elements\u2014offer and acceptance, consideration, mutuality or intention, legality, and capacity. Consideration refers to the benefit that both parties receive, such as money, services, or anything of value. Offer and acceptance refers to one party offering something and the other party accepting it. Legality refers to the contract obeying federal, state, and local laws. Capacity refers to all parties being legally able to sign the contract. SOURCE: BL:002 Describe the nature of legally binding contracts SOURCE: Adobe. (2024). What is a binding vs. non-binding contract? Retrieved October 10, 2024, from https://www.adobe.com/acrobat/business/hub/binding-vs-non-binding-contract.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q2", "number": 2, "question": "Jan works from home, and she needs to ask her team leader a quick question and share a screenshot. Which staff communication channel would be most efficient?", "options": ["Instant messaging app", "Video conference", "Project management platform", "Document sharing platform"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Instant messaging app. Instant messaging works well for remote workers, as the team leader can manage all members and collaborate in real time. Asking a quick question and sharing a screenshot via an instant messaging app is the most efficient channel of staff communication for both Jan and her team leader. A project management platform is primarily used to coordinate staff activity and communicate with large teams. Video conferences are often used to host interviews, meetings, training sessions, web seminars, or creative scrums. Document sharing platforms allow companies to share information contained in large files. SOURCE: CO:014 Explain the nature of staff communication SOURCE: Indeed. (2024, June 27). What are staff communications (Types and importance)? Retrieved September 17, 2024, from https://uk.indeed.com/career-advice/career-development/staff-communications"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q3", "number": 3, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a general goal:", "options": ["Donate $500 each month to an organization", "Spend 10 hours per week on a project", "Increase sales by 5% each quarter", "Decrease costs and expenses"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Decrease costs and expenses. A goal is a statement that clearly describes a task to be accomplished. Some goals are general and some are specific. Decreasing costs and expenses is an example of a general goal. Increasing sales by 5% each quarter, spending 10 hours per week on a project, and donating $500 each month to an organization are each examples of specific goals. SOURCE: MK:015 Discuss actions employees can take to achieve the company's desired results SOURCE: LAP-MK-015\u2014Act Now! (Employee Actions and Company Goals)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q4", "number": 4, "question": "Target collects information on the physical and social characteristics of the population during its environmental scanning efforts. Target is obtaining information on", "options": ["demographics.", "society and culture.", "the economy.", "competition."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Demographics. The physical and social characteristics of the population are called demographics. The economy refers to economic factors such as the stage of the business cycle, inflation, interest rates, unemployment rates, etc. Society and culture refer to ever-changing customer values and attitudes as society evolves. Obtaining information on competition involves observing what other companies do with a similar product and then creating strategies to do it better. SOURCE: NF:015 Conduct an environmental scan to obtain business information SOURCE: LAP-NF-015\u2014Get the 4-1-1 (Conducting an Environmental Scan)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q5", "number": 5, "question": "Which of the following is a quantitative data collection method:", "options": ["Observation", "Focus group", "Personal interview", "Experiment"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Experiment. Quantitative data are numbers and statistics. Some common quantitative data collection methods are experiments, surveys, and tracking. Personal interviews, focus groups, and observation are qualitative data collection methods. Qualitative data is information that is descriptive and nonstatistical in nature. SOURCE: IM:289 Describe data-collection methods (e.g., observations, mail, diaries, phone, internet, discussion groups, interviews, scanners, tracking tools) SOURCE: LAP-IM-289\u2014Hunting and Gathering (Data Collection Methods)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q6", "number": 6, "question": "When Nadine announces she made her 100th sale, her coworker Esteban offers to buy her lunch to celebrate. Instead of feeling jealous of Nadine\u2019s success, Esteban congratulates her. Esteban is demonstrating how to", "options": ["be cooperative.", "respect privacy.", "be humble.", "carry his own weight."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Be cooperative. A work team runs more smoothly with cooperation and teamwork, which includes celebrating when something good happens to a coworker, rather than being jealous or resentful. Carrying your own weight refers to doing your job, meeting your deadlines, and being responsible. Being humble refers to not having an arrogant attitude. Respecting privacy refers to avoiding eavesdropping. SOURCE: EI:037 Foster positive working relationships SOURCE: LAP-EI-037\u2014Can You Relate? (Fostering Positive Working Relationships)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q7", "number": 7, "question": "To build rapport with customers, Gretchen often imitates their tone and language. Gretchen is using", "options": ["affinity.", "reciprocity.", "mirroring.", "mimicking."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Mirroring. Mirroring is the act of imitating the actions or words of others. Mirroring a customer\u2019s tone, language, or volume level (within reason) can communicate that you\u2019re on the same page as them. Reciprocity is the idea that creating value for your customers prompts them to give you something in return. Affinity refers to a spontaneous or natural liking or sympathy for someone or something. Mimicking is a form of imitation, but its purpose is typically to entertain or ridicule. SOURCE: CR:029 Develop rapport with customers SOURCE: Inabo, S. (2024, March 15). What is customer rapport? (+8 ways to build it). Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://www.zendesk.com/blog/customer-rapport"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q8", "number": 8, "question": "A baseball equipment manufacturer discovers that its products are arriving at retail stores several days after they are scheduled. The manufacturer becomes upset with the wholesaler, who is responsible for shipping the products to the retailers. This scenario best describes __________ conflict.", "options": ["horizontal", "multiple-channel", "vertical", "internal"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Vertical. Vertical conflict is a type of channel conflict that occurs between channel members at different levels within the same channel. Because the manufacturer and wholesaler in this scenario are at different levels in the same channel, this is an example of vertical conflict. Horizontal conflict is a type of channel conflict that occurs between channel members at the same level (e.g., two retailers). Multiple-channel conflict is a type of conflict that occurs among members of two or more channels of distribution that compete in the same market for a particular producer. Internal conflict refers to conflicting thoughts or ideas within yourself. SOURCE: CM:008 Explain the nature of channel-member relationships SOURCE: Mack, S. (2024). Horizontal and vertical marketing conflicts. Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/horizontal-vertical-marketing-conflicts-65325.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q9", "number": 9, "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using technology in channel management:", "options": ["High initial investments", "Longer delivery times", "Less personalized experiences", "Streamlined processes"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Streamlined processes. Channel management refers to the processes by which marketers ensure products are distributed to customers efficiently and effectively. Technology has had a substantial impact on the way businesses manage their distribution channels. For instance, technology has allowed businesses to automate many of their repetitive tasks (such as order processing and inventory management), which helps to streamline processes and increase overall efficiency, profitability, and customer satisfaction. Longer delivery times, less personalized experiences, and high initial investments are not advantages of using technology in channel management. SOURCE: CM:004 Describe the use of technology in the channel management function SOURCE: Ingram, D. (n.d.). Channel management techniques. Retrieved September 16, 2024, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/channel-management-techniques-3072.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q10", "number": 10, "question": "A multinational technology company organizes a cookout for the local township in which it is located. This is an example of what kind of public relations activity?", "options": ["Public affairs", "Community relations", "Employee relations", "Crisis management"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Community relations. Community relations focuses on developing a business's relationship with the local community, often by organizing events, visiting schools or businesses, giving back to the community, etc. Public affairs, or lobbying, focuses on government and legislative changes. Crisis management is a business's response after a disaster. Employee relations, or internal public relations, involves employee communications and events. SOURCE: PR:252 Identify types of public-relations activities SOURCE: Bright Network. (2024). A guide to the different types of PR. Retrieved October 12, 2024, from https://www.brightnetwork.co.uk/career-path-guides/marketing-pr/different-types-pr/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q11", "number": 11, "question": "Which of the following statements about executive summaries is true:", "options": ["They are frequently distributed to low-level employees.", "They help readers make decisions without reading the whole report.", "They can be written using a casual voice.", "They are dense documents that omit little to no information."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "They help readers make decisions without reading the whole report. An executive summary provides readers with an overview of the main points of a larger report so they can make informed decisions without needing to read the entire report. Executive summaries are frequently written for leaders in a business or organization, such as CEOs, department heads, or supervisors, so they can get critical information quickly to decide a course of action. An executive summary omits unnecessary information, ensuring that key information can be delivered quickly and cohesively. An executive summary should always be written using a professional voice. SOURCE: CO:091 Write executive summaries SOURCE: University of Arizona Global Campus Writing Center. (2023). Writing an executive summary. Retrieved September 17, 2024, from https://writingcenter.uagc.edu/writing-executive-summary"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q12", "number": 12, "question": "Only six months after buying a new truck, Parker has to take it to his local mechanic. After inspection, he learns that the needed repair is not covered by the warranty, which only covers specific parts of the car. This best describes a(n) __________ warranty.", "options": ["express", "implied", "limited", "full"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Limited. A limited warranty is a warranty that does not contain the provisions of a full warranty and may only cover specific parts, certain repairs, or a particular time period. Because the warranty for Parker's truck only covers certain parts, this scenario describes a limited warranty. A full warranty covers the entire product. An implied warranty is an unwritten, unspoken warranty understood by the customer and the seller that the product will perform as expected. An express warranty is a promise expressed in a specific statement concerning the quality of the product, and is written or stated verbally. SOURCE: PM:020 Explain warranties and guarantees SOURCE: LAP-PM-920\u2014Promises, Promises (Warranties and Guarantees)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q13", "number": 13, "question": "A company purchases large quantities of goods directly from manufacturers and then sells these goods to various small businesses, which, in turn, sell them to individual consumers. Based on this information, what type of business is this company most likely to be?", "options": ["Agent", "Wholesaler", "Retailer", "Producers"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Wholesaler. Wholesalers are businesses that buy goods from producers or agents and sell them to retailers. Because the company bought goods directly from a manufacturer and sells them to various small businesses, which often includes retailers, this company is a wholesaler. A retailer is a business that buys consumer goods or services and sells them to the ultimate consumer. Agents are businesses or individuals that assist in the sale or promotion of goods and services but do not buy them from the producer. Producers make or provide goods and services. SOURCE: CM:003 Explain the nature of channels of distribution SOURCE: LAP-CM-003\u2014Channel It (Channels of Distribution)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q14", "number": 14, "question": "When a leader relies on bullying and threats to influence the behavior of others, they are utilizing __________ power.", "options": ["coercive", "reward", "legitimate", "referent"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Coercive. When people use coercive power, they force their followers to do things against their will by setting up consequences for failure to complete the desired task. Coercive leaders often rely on bullying and threats to influence the behavior of others. Reward power involves the use of prizes and incentives to motivate someone to complete a desired task. People that have authority, such as government officials, have legitimate power \u2013 the power of position or role. When people are able to attract the loyalty and respect of others, they have referent power. SOURCE: EI:135 Use power appropriately SOURCE: LAP-EI-135\u2014Power Play (Using Power Appropriately)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q15", "number": 15, "question": "Which of the following scenarios best illustrates a company using primary data in marketing research:", "options": ["A business uses data from past customer surveys to improve future products.", "A company conducts interviews with potential customers to understand preferences.", "A retailer analyzes its sales reports to identify trends over the past year.", "A research organization compiles industry reports to assess market trends."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "A company conducts interviews with potential customers to understand preferences. Primary data come from new research an organization carries out on its own initiative\u2014a customer survey, interview, or focus group, for example. Therefore, a company conducting interviews with potential customers to understand their preferences is an example of a company using primary data. Secondary data come from research that is already available\u2014financial records, sales invoices, customer databases, and public investment information are just a few examples. A retailer analyzing its sales reports to identify trends over the past year, a research organization compiling industry reports to assess market trends, and a business using data from past customer surveys to improve future products are examples of secondary data. SOURCE: IM:184 Identify data monitored for marketing decision making SOURCE: LAP-IM-184\u2014Data Diving (Identifying Marketing Data)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q16", "number": 16, "question": "After Brock makes a sale to a new client, that new client connects Brock with other businesses that might be interested in his company\u2019s product. What type of client-building benefit is this?", "options": ["A service attitude", "Repeat sales", "Referrals", "Loyalty"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Referrals. Referrals are individuals or businesses to whom salespeople are recommended. Loyal customers often provide salespeople with leads to new clients. Repeat sales are sales made to the same customer over and over again. A service attitude reflects a strong commitment to the client and their needs. SOURCE: SE:828 Explain key factors in building a clientele SOURCE: LAP-SE-828\u2014Keep Them Loyal (Key Factors in Building Clientele)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q17", "number": 17, "question": "June looks up to Amelia Earhart for her bravery, determination, and passion. While June wants to work in business rather than aviation when she is older, she still hopes to imitate Amelia\u2019s behavior in her professional career. Amelia Earhart can be best characterized as June\u2019s", "options": ["colleague.", "coach.", "role model.", "manager."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Role model. A role model is a person who is admired and considered a guide for the choices, actions, and behaviors of others. Because June admires Amelia\u2019s bravery, determination, and passion, and hopes to embody that behavior herself, June treats Amelia as her role model. June does not know or work with Amelia, so Amelia cannot be her manager, coach, or colleague. SOURCE: EI:002 Assess personal strengths and weaknesses SOURCE: LAP-EI-902\u2014Assess for Success (Assessing Personal Strengths and Weaknesses)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q18", "number": 18, "question": "A superstore lowers the prices of several products to increase sales. However, the opposite happens\u2014customers buy less of these products. This is an example of why prices should be", "options": ["universal.", "realistic.", "competitive.", "flexible."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Realistic. Believe it or not, prices can be set too low. Many businesses have found that if their prices are not what customers expect to pay, even if that price is lower than expected, customers will not buy. Customers associate price with quality\u2014if the price is high, the quality is high; if the price is low, the quality is low. Businesses must set prices that are realistic to customers\u2014neither too high nor too low. This is not an example of why it is important for prices to be flexible, competitive, or universal. SOURCE: PI:001 Explain the nature and scope of the pricing function SOURCE: LAP-PI-001\u2014The Price Is Right (Nature of Pricing)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q19", "number": 19, "question": "Lisa is an actress and the director tells her that she has free range to make decisions and interpret her character. Lisa\u2019s job is", "options": ["high-scope.", "high-depth.", "low-scope.", "low-depth."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "High-depth. High-depth jobs normally include opportunities for decision-making and allow employees to set their own pace. A low-depth job contains strict guidelines that you must follow, and you have very few decisions to make. High-scope jobs require you to perform several different operations on the job. They contain less repetition and more variation (think of the numerous different tasks a mechanic could perform on the job). Meanwhile, low-scope jobs only require you to perform one specialized skill repeatedly. They are high in repetition and low in variation. SOURCE: EC:014 Analyze impact of specialization/division of labor on productivity SOURCE: LAP-EC-914\u2014Divide and Conquer (Specialization and Division of Labor)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q20", "number": 20, "question": "Why might a business opt to develop a shorter-range sales forecast instead of a longer-range sales forecast?", "options": ["Longer-range sales forecasts are more accurate.", "Longer-range sales forecasts are more consistent.", "Shorter-range sales forecasts are more reliable.", "Shorter-range sales forecasts are more expensive."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Shorter-range sales forecasts are more reliable. Businesses use shorter-range sales forecasts more commonly than longer-range ones because they are more reliable. Short-range forecasting predicts sales for periods of less than three months, and businesses often use short-range forecasts to aid in day-to-day decision-making regarding planning, scheduling, staffing, inventory, etc. Longer-range sales forecasts are less accurate, more expensive, and less consistent than shorter-range forecasts. SOURCE: MP:013 Explain the nature of sales forecasts SOURCE: LAP-MP-013\u2014Futurecast (The Nature of Sales Forecasts)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q21", "number": 21, "question": "Which of the following scenarios best demonstrates ethical marketing:", "options": ["Molly strives for transparency in her marketing.", "Doug uses aggressive sales tactics.", "Keyanna shares information with competitors.", "D'Angelo exaggerates benefits when promoting products."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Molly strives for transparency in her marketing. Marketing is an organizational function and a set of processes for creating, communicating, and delivering value to customers and for managing customer relations in ways that benefit the organization and its stakeholders. According to the American Marketing Association, ethical marketing involves striving for transparency and fairness in all aspects of marketing. Using aggressive sales tactics, sharing information with competitors, and exaggerating benefits when promoting products do not demonstrate ethical marketing. SOURCE: PD:137 Explain the need for professional and ethical standards in marketing SOURCE: American Marketing Association. (2021, May). AMA statement of ethics. Retrieved September 16, 2024, from https://www.ama.org/ama-statement-of-ethics"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q22", "number": 22, "question": "A divisional organizational structure is often broken down by", "options": ["customer type.", "manager.", "function.", "job type."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Customer type. A divisional organizational structure is often broken down into units by product, by process, by territory, or by customer type. The traditional functional structure is broken down by function (sales, marketing, etc.). No common organizational designs are divided by manager or job type. SOURCE: EC:103 Explain the organizational design of businesses SOURCE: LAP-EC-103\u2014Designed to Work (Organizational Design of Businesses)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q23", "number": 23, "question": "In the early days of the iPhone, owning one was considered a luxury, but now they have become an essential part of our daily lives and it seems like everybody has one. This is an example of __________ innovation.", "options": ["positioning", "product", "paradigm", "process"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Paradigm. Paradigm innovation is a significant change in the way a product is viewed by users and society at large. The change in the way the iPhone is viewed by users and society is an example of paradigm innovation. Process innovation is a change in how something is done. Positioning innovation occurs when the purpose of a product is changed. Product innovation occurs when a business either creates or improves a product. SOURCE: PD:126 Explain the need for innovation skills SOURCE: LAP-PD-126\u2014Ideas in Action (Innovation Skills)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q24", "number": 24, "question": "Which of the following actions should you take to ensure safety while working with dangerous equipment and machinery:", "options": ["Report any safety concerns after you finish your shift to keep productivity levels high.", "Use the equipment before reviewing the operating manual to test it out.", "Shorten training procedures for coworkers who have used the machinery before.", "Return ill-fitting personal protective equipment for the appropriate size."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Return ill-fitting personal protective equipment for the appropriate size. Personal protective equipment must be the correct size and properly fitted to be effective and safe. Returning ill-fitting personal protective equipment for the appropriate size helps ensure safety while working with dangerous machinery. Using equipment before reviewing the operating manual is dangerous. Even if coworkers have used the machinery before, they should still participate in all training procedures. Safety concerns should be reported immediately. SOURCE: OP:442 Comply with policies and procedures for use of property and equipment SOURCE: Oboloo. (2024). The ultimate guide to understanding your company\u2019s equipment policy for procurement. Retrieved September 13, 2024, from https://oboloo.com/the-ultimate-guide-to-understanding-your-companys-equipment-policy-for-procurement/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q25", "number": 25, "question": "Which of the following can help accentuate the primary feature of an ad:", "options": ["Using clip art", "Using white space", "Using smaller fonts", "Using just one color"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Using white space. White space is blank space in a print advertisement that is unoccupied by text or illustrations. White space helps put focus on a specific aspect of an advertisement. Using smaller fonts, just one color, or clip art can be distracting design strategies that will not help accentuate primary features of an ad. SOURCE: PR:251 Explain the importance of coordinating elements in advertisements SOURCE: Stribely, M. (2024). 10 rules of composition all designers live by. Retrieved October 15, 2024, from https://www.canva.com/learn/visual-design-composition"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q26", "number": 26, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a marketing professional demonstrating objectivity:", "options": ["Rio accepts responsibility for their decisions and is liable for their actions.", "Rachel doesn't allow her own personal needs to impact her decision-making.", "Arlo maintains open and honest communications with his colleagues.", "Ishmael ensures that the information he manages is believable."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Rachel doesn't allow her own personal needs to impact her decision-making. Objectivity means viewing things in an unbiased manner. When you are objective, like Rachel in this scenario, you do not allow your own personal needs and desires to impact your decision-making. Marketing information needs to be objective because biased information is not helpful, useful, or fair. Arlo is demonstrating transparency, which means maintaining truthful and open communications. Ishmael is demonstrating credibility (believability), as it is critical that marketers ensure the information they manage is believable. Rio is demonstrating accountability, which is accepting responsibility for your decisions and being liable for your actions. SOURCE: IM:025 Explain the role of ethics in marketing-information management SOURCE: LAP-IM-025\u2014Info With Integrity (Ethics in Marketing-Information Management)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q27", "number": 27, "question": "Jameera, the project manager for an engineering firm, was given a new project to lead. After identifying the project's stakeholders and planning communications and meetings, what is the next logical step that Jameera should take in the project planning process?", "options": ["Obtain feedback from her team", "Create a schedule", "Define the project scope", "Identify potential risks"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Define the project scope. After identifying the project's stakeholders and planning communications and meetings, Jameera would then define the project scope. A project\u2019s scope is what the project will and will not include. Scope is one of the most important aspects of the planning process because it defines what the project actually is and what the end results will be. It\u2019s important to define these parameters ahead of time because otherwise, you might try to do too much or not enough. After defining the project scope, Jameera will break down the work; identify resources; create a schedule; develop quality standards; identify risks; develop a draft plan by combining dates, deliverables, and resources; and obtain feedback from her team and refine the plan. SOURCE: OP:519 Plan project SOURCE: LAP-OP-519\u2014Plan On It! (Planning Projects)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q28", "number": 28, "question": "The Cleveland Browns are promoting new merchandise for fans. Which of the following is a technique the marketing team can use to ensure they avoid stereotypes and sexism in their advertisements:", "options": ["Consider the intent of their advertisements over the impact.", "Cast men of different races and ethnicities in their commercials.", "Gather feedback from a diverse focus group.", "Center the advertisement around a timely environmental issue."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Gather feedback from a diverse focus group. A diverse focus group offers feedback from multiple perspectives which helps marketing teams detect stereotypes and sexism in their advertisements before they air. While it is wise to cast people of different races and ethnicities, casting exclusively men is sexist and perpetuates the stereotype that only men enjoy football. Centering the advertisement around a timely environmental issue would not help avoid stereotypes and sexism in their advertisements. Ethical marketers should always consider impact over intent. SOURCE: PR:099 Describe the use of business ethics in promotion SOURCE: LAP-PR-099\u2014Fear Factor (Ethics in Promotion)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q29", "number": 29, "question": "After several of its customers fell ill after eating its product, a food company issued a recall. It also sent out press releases to inform the public about what it was doing to resolve the situation. This is an example of what type of institutional promotion?", "options": ["Patronage", "Primary", "Public service", "Public relations"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Public relations. Public relations promotions are created to deal with issues that are in the public\u2019s interest but are also related to the company or its products. These promotional activities may be either proactive (the business takes the initiative to promote itself) or reactive (the business engages in the activities in response to an external situation, such as a lawsuit). Patronage promotions are designed to promote a firm\u2019s prestige or its features. Public service promotions are used to inform customers about noncontroversial issues that are in the public\u2019s best interest. Primary product promotion aims to stimulate demand, or desire, for an entire class of goods or services. Primary product promotion is not a type of institutional promotion. SOURCE: PR:002 Explain the types of promotion (i.e., institutional, product) SOURCE: LAP-PR-902\u2014Know Your Options (Product and Institutional Promotion)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q30", "number": 30, "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of word-of-mouth advertising:", "options": ["Low cost", "Limited control", "Unpredictability", "Limited reach"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Low cost. Word-of-mouth advertising is promotion and publicity for a business provided by customers who tell others of their satisfaction with the business. This is a low-cost marketing strategy because it relies on customers \u201cdoing the work\u201d for the business. Limited control, unpredictability, and limited reach are all disadvantages of word-of-mouth advertising. SOURCE: PR:247 Describe word-of-mouth channels used to communicate with targeted audiences SOURCE: Hayes, A. (2024, July 2). Word-of-mouth marketing: Meaning and uses in business. Retrieved October 2, 2024, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/w/word-of-mouth-marketing.asp"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q31", "number": 31, "question": "Which of the following is a way in which technology impacts marketing-information management:", "options": ["It eliminates all risks a business may face.", "It ensures employees are happy in their jobs.", "It helps companies gather customer data.", "It helps to limit the impact of competition."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "It helps companies gather customer data. The main role of information technology in marketing management is to help gather data about customers. The proper gathering, managing, and analyzing of customer data ensures businesses are up to date on the market and their customers' needs and expectations. Technology in marketing-information management does not ensure employees are happy in their jobs nor help to limit the impact of competition. Although technology may help a business to better predict and manage risk, it will not completely eliminate all risks. SOURCE: IM:183 Describe the use of technology in the marketing-information management function SOURCE: Vaia. (2024). Marketing information management. Retrieved September 23, 2024, from https://www.vaia.com/en-us/explanations/marketing/marketing-information-management"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q32", "number": 32, "question": "A local bakery expects monthly cash sales to be $15,500 and interest income to be $2,500. The bakery's total cost of goods will be $9,250, while its fixed expenses will be $3,150 and variable expenses will be $2,975. What is the cash flow?", "options": ["-$2,425", "$8,925", "$2,625", "-$8,575"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "$2,625. Cash flow is calculated by subtracting total cash paid out from total cash receipts. Total cash receipts include cash sales and interest income ($15,500 + $2,500 = $18,000). Total cash paid out includes cost of goods, fixed expenses, and variable expenses ($9,250 + $3,150 + $2,975 = $15,375). Subtract total cash paid out from total cash receipts to determine cash flow ($18,000 - $15,375 = $2,625). SOURCE: FI:091 Describe the nature of cash flow statements SOURCE: LAP-FI-091\u2014Count the Cash (Cash Flow Statements)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q33", "number": 33, "question": "Nicole owns a carpentry shop and positions her brand by highlighting the superior craftsmanship of her products and her employees\u2019 expertise. What type of brand positioning is Nicole utilizing?", "options": ["Quality-based positioning", "Benefit positioning", "Competitor-based positioning", "Problem/Solution positioning"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Quality-based positioning. Nicole is utilizing quality-based brand positioning by highlighting the superior quality of her products and services. Benefit positioning focuses on the unique benefits that consumers can only gain from the brand\u2019s product or service. Problem/Solution positioning addresses a specific problem the brand\u2019s target audience faces and positions the brand as the solution. Competitor-based positioning differentiates the brand from a competitor\u2019s based on factors like product features, customer service, or pricing. SOURCE: PM:207 Describe factors used by businesses to position corporate brands SOURCE: Bartolacci, G. (2022, October 20). 14 examples of strong brand positioning and why they work. Retrieved October 9, 2024, from https://www.newbreedrevenue.com/blog/7-examples-of-strong-brand-positioning-and-why-they-work"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q34", "number": 34, "question": "A research team finds enough existing data to support its research. In this scenario, the team used __________ data.", "options": ["training", "primary", "secondary", "big"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Secondary. Secondary data are data that already exist and have been used for another purpose (e.g., sales invoices, expense reports). Because the research team in the scenario is using existing data to support its research, it is using secondary data. Primary data are new data obtained through surveys, focus groups, etc. Big data refers to large amounts of raw information automatically collected from electronic sources (such as mobile apps, website cookies, and store loyalty cards). Training data is data used to teach machine learning models, such as AI, how to perform a specific function. SOURCE: IM:282 Discuss the nature of marketing research problems/issues SOURCE: LAP-IM-282\u2014What\u2019s the Problem? (Marketing Research Problems)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q35", "number": 35, "question": "While assessing the quality of a source, Martha realizes it was published nearly 15 years ago and worries the information will no longer be relevant. The issue with this source is its", "options": ["bias.", "timeliness.", "reliability.", "validity."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Timeliness. Timeliness means ensuring the source was published or last updated recently enough to be relevant to your topic. Bias means the source favors or opposes a particular person or thing. Validity means the information in the source is logical and factual. Reliability is the degree to which the information is accurate and consistent and can be used to make informed decisions. SOURCE: NF:079 Evaluate quality and source of information SOURCE: Central Michigan University Libraries. (2024, September 17). Online research: CRAAP test. Retrieved September 25, 2024, from https://libguides.cmich.edu/web_research/craap"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q36", "number": 36, "question": "How can companies use standard deviation to make better marketing decisions?", "options": ["By measuring the level of risk in stock prices or customer churn rates", "By uncovering the most popular product features or customer preferences", "By identifying the average sales price", "By determining the most representative marketing trend"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "By measuring the level of risk in stock prices or customer churn rates. Standard deviation can be used by companies to measure the level of risk or volatility in market data, such as stock prices or customer churn rates. Identifying the average sales price requires companies to calculate the mean. Determining the most representative marketing trend requires companies to locate the median. Uncovering the most popular product features or customer preferences requires companies to find the mode. SOURCE: IM:191 Explain the use of descriptive statistics in marketing decision making SOURCE: Editverse. (2024). The role of descriptive statistics in understanding market dynamics. Retrieved October 2, 2024, from https://editverse.com/descriptive-statistics-market-dynamics/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q37", "number": 37, "question": "Garrett is evaluating whether potential customers have the capital and interest in purchasing his company\u2019s products. Garrett is in the process of", "options": ["prescribing solutions to customer needs.", "qualifying sales leads.", "generating sales leads.", "identifying features and benefits."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Qualifying sales leads. By determining if potential customers have the money and interest to patronize his company, Garrett is qualifying sales leads. Generating sales leads means looking for potential customers. Identifying features and benefits means learning to explain to customers the advantages the product will bring them. Prescribing solutions to customer needs is a later step in the selling process that involves giving a sales presentation. SOURCE: SE:048 Explain the selling process SOURCE: LAP-SE-048\u2014Set Your Sales (The Selling Process)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q38", "number": 38, "question": "An ice cream parlor has an \u201cedge\u201d over its competition because it offers flavors that cannot be found anywhere else. This is an example of a(n)", "options": ["target market.", "determinant factor.", "endorsement.", "competitive advantage."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Competitive advantage. A competitive advantage is any \u201cedge\u201d a company has that allows it to create more sales, generate more revenue, retain more customers, etc., than its competition. In this scenario, the ice cream parlor's \"edge,\" or competitive advantage, is that it offers flavors that cannot be found anywhere else. This is not an example of a target market, a determinant factor, or an endorsement. A target market refers to the particular group of customers a business seeks to attract. A determinant factor is an aspect of a product or brand that the target market really cares about\u2014something that makes a big difference to a target customer. An endorsement is approval by a reputable external source. SOURCE: PM:042 Describe factors used by marketers to position products/services SOURCE: LAP-PM-042\u2014Getting Piece of Mind (Factors Used To Position Products/Services)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q39", "number": 39, "question": "Which of the following is an example of marketing literature that can provide useful product information:", "options": ["Newsletters", "Internal sales records", "Industry publications", "Sales receipts"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Newsletters. Newsletters are marketing tools used to share product or business information with stakeholders. Internal sales records are for company use and are not marketing tools. Industry publications are trade-related magazines or periodicals\u2014they are not considered marketing literature. Sales receipts can offer useful financial or accounting information but are unlikely to provide useful information for use in selling. SOURCE: SE:062 Acquire product information for use in selling SOURCE: LAP-SE-062\u2014Get Informed (Acquiring Product Information for Use in Selling)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q40", "number": 40, "question": "Which of the following statements about surveys is true:", "options": ["They should be written in plain, simple language.", "They should typically take about an hour to complete.", "Sensitive questions should be placed at the beginning.", "Each question should focus on multiple topics."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "They should be written in plain, simple language. When creating a survey, there are a few important characteristics to keep in mind. Surveys should be written in plain, simple language. By using the most accessible language you can, it ensures respondents understand the survey and are able to answer appropriately. Each survey question should have a single focus, rather than focusing on multiple topics. Sensitive questions should be placed toward the end of the survey, rather than the beginning. Surveys should typically take about five minutes to complete, but no more than 10 to 15 minutes. A survey longer than 15 minutes may cause the respondent to lose interest, not answer appropriately, or not finish the survey entirely. SOURCE: IM:418 Explain characteristics of effective data-collection instruments SOURCE: Qualtrics. (2024). Survey question sequence, flow & style. Retrieved September 23, 2024, from https://www.qualtrics.com/experience-management/research/question-sequence-flow-style"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q41", "number": 41, "question": "When products are sold across state lines, they must meet interstate commerce and transportation standards set by", "options": ["businesses.", "the government.", "professional organizations.", "trade associations."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "The government. When businesses sell their products across state lines, they must meet government standards for interstate commerce and transportation. Businesses, trade associations, and professional organizations do not set the standards for interstate commerce and transportation. SOURCE: PM:019 Describe the uses of grades and standards in marketing SOURCE: LAP-PM-019\u2014Raise the Bar (Grades and Standards)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q42", "number": 42, "question": "Which of the following is a generally accepted coding principle:", "options": ["Repeat code whenever possible", "Make code open to extension", "Make code open to modification", "The longer the code, the better"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Make code open to extension. Coding is the process of writing instructions for computers to follow to complete tasks or perform actions. There are several generally accepted coding principles, including the open-closed principle. This principle states that code should be open to extension, but closed for modification. Essentially, this means that you should be able to add new functionality without changing the existing code. Rather than writing long code, it is important to keep it as simple as possible. You should avoid repeating or duplicating code. SOURCE: IM:062 Explain techniques for processing marketing data SOURCE: Mr. Unity Buddy. (2021, September 20). Top 10 coding principles every developer must know. Retrieved September 25, 2024, from https://dev.to/unitybuddy/top-10-coding-principles-every-developer-must-know-2gk4"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q43", "number": 43, "question": "Prajeeth scrolls past numerous advertisements from clothing companies on TikTok. Which of the following is the most logical explanation:", "options": ["Prajeeth frequently shops online for clothes.", "Prajeeth recently adjusted his advertisement preference settings to exclude clothing companies.", "Prajeeth works for a clothing company.", "Prajeeth accidentally subscribed to each company\u2019s advertising channel."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Prajeeth frequently shops online for clothes. Advertisers collect data on consumers\u2019 browsing history and interactions with websites and then use that data to target advertisements specifically to the consumer. Hence, the most logical explanation for why Prajeeth receives so many advertisements from clothing companies is that he frequently shops online and interacts with clothing companies\u2019 websites. It is less logical that Prajeeth accidentally subscribed to each company\u2019s advertising channel. Prajeeth\u2019s place of employment does not necessarily impact the types of advertisements he encounters. If Prajeeth had recently adjusted his advertisement preference settings to exclude clothing companies, the advertisements would not have appeared. SOURCE: PR:100 Describe the use of technology in the promotion function SOURCE: Lau, W. (2024, June 30). What is targeted advertising? Retrieved October 14, 2024, from https://www.adroll.com/blog/what-is-targeted-advertising"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q44", "number": 44, "question": "Psychographic segmentation divides a market based on customers'", "options": ["lifestyles and personalities.", "socioeconomic status.", "gender and location.", "origin or heritage."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Lifestyles and personalities. Psychographic segmentation is the division of a market on the basis of customers' lifestyles and personalities. Lifestyle refers to the way in which people lead their daily lives as determined by their income, interests, and activities, while personality is defined by a person's individual qualities or traits and behavior. Origin, heritage, socioeconomic status, and gender are all characteristics taken into account during demographic segmentation\u2014the division of a market on the basis of its physical and social characteristics. Geographic segmentation is the division of a market on the basis of where customers are located. SOURCE: MP:003 Explain the concept of market and market identification SOURCE: LAP-MP-003\u2014Have We Met? (Market Identification)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q45", "number": 45, "question": "Inflation is a(n) __________ trend.", "options": ["international", "predictable", "devastating", "general"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "General. It\u2019s important to note that inflation is a general trend. The average prices of goods and services in an economy may go up over a certain period of time, but that doesn\u2019t mean that the price of each individual product has gotten higher. As a matter of fact, the prices of some products may even go down. Inflation cannot always be predicted. A little bit of inflation is actually a good thing\u2014not necessarily devastating. Inflation does not impact different countries equally, so it is not an international trend. SOURCE: EC:083 Describe the economic impact of inflation on business SOURCE: LAP-EC-083\u2014Up, Up, and Away (Inflation)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q46", "number": 46, "question": "Which of the following is a way in which technology enhances pricing decisions:", "options": ["It ensures customers will buy products.", "It allows for personalized pricing and discounts.", "It prevents businesses from changing prices in real time.", "It guarantees an increase in profits."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "It allows for personalized pricing and discounts. Technology has been a game-changer in pricing strategy by changing the way businesses collect, analyze, and use data to make pricing decisions. It has allowed businesses to offer personalized pricing, discounts, and promotions, which helps to increase both customer satisfaction and loyalty. Technology can certainly help businesses increase profits and lead to customers buying more products, but neither is guaranteed. Technology allows businesses to change prices in real time. SOURCE: PI:016 Explain the use of technology in the pricing function SOURCE: Jennings Executive Search. (2024). Emerging technologies in pricing strategy: A guide for businesses. Retrieved January 24, 2025, from https://jenningsexec.com/emerging-technologies-in-pricing-strategy"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q47", "number": 47, "question": "Pablo has failed to make payments on his debt for the last several months. His employer will now withhold a portion of Pablo\u2019s paychecks to pay for the debt. This situation is best described as", "options": ["foreclosure.", "angel investment.", "repossession.", "wage garnishment."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Wage garnishment. Wage garnishment is a legal procedure in which a person\u2019s earnings are required by court order to be withheld by an employer for the payment of a debt. Repossession is the action of retaking possession of something when a buyer defaults on payments. Foreclosure involves the repossession of a mortgaged property when a tenant fails to keep up on their mortgage payments. Angel investors provide startup money to new businesses. SOURCE: FI:568 Control debt SOURCE: Laurence, B.K. (2024, June 12). What can creditors do if you don\u2019t pay? Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/free-books/small-business-book/chapter4-4.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q48", "number": 48, "question": "When a business can't clearly define its reasons for research, it often focuses on qualitative data to help determine how to proceed with its research. This best describes which of the following types of research:", "options": ["Predictive", "Exploratory", "Casual", "Descriptive"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Exploratory. Exploratory research is marketing research that collects information to help the business define its issue, situation, or concern and decide how to proceed with its research. Exploratory research typically focuses on qualitative data, such as respondents\u2019 opinions and personal interpretations rather than facts and figures. Descriptive research is used to gather specific data\u2014such as facts, statistics, and figures\u2014related to the identified research problem. Such data are quantitative data: The facts and figures can be presented in the form of a chart or graph. Causal research, sometimes called conclusive research, focuses on cause-and-effect relationships and tests \u201cwhat if\u201d theories. It determines the impact that one item or entity has on another. Businesses use predictive research to help them forecast future business developments, such as estimating future sales, predicting the growth or decline of a market, or projecting consumer tastes. SOURCE: IM:010 Explain the nature of marketing research SOURCE: LAP-IM-010\u2014Seek and Find (Marketing Research)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q49", "number": 49, "question": "Which of the following best demonstrates an activity involved with environmental scanning:", "options": ["A corporation conducts a financial audit.", "A business modernizes its internal policies.", "An organization hires a new human resources manager.", "A company investigates its competitors."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "A company investigates its competitors. Environmental scanning refers to collecting information about the environment surrounding your business. Investigating competition, keeping up with economic trends, and staying up to date on new technology are some common activities involved with environmental scanning. Conducting financial audits, hiring a new human resources manager, and modernizing internal policies are each internal business activities rather than external, and therefore not typically involved with environmental scanning. SOURCE: MP:008 Explain the role of situation analysis in the marketing planning process SOURCE: Gosnell, K. (2023, March 22). Environmental scanning: How CEOs can stay ahead of the curve and beat the competition. Retrieved September 19, 2024, from https://www.business.com/articles/what-is-environmental-scanning"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q50", "number": 50, "question": "The primary role of promotion is to __________ demand for products.", "options": ["discourage", "investigate", "increase", "maintain"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Increase. Promotion encourages demand by informing consumers about products, reminding them of the existence of products, and influencing their decisions to buy. Decreasing demand would be contrary to the role of promotion. While some processes within promotion may involve maintaining or investigating demand, the primary role of promotion is still to increase demand. SOURCE: PR:001 Explain the role of promotion as a marketing function SOURCE: LAP-PR-901\u2014Razzle Dazzle (Nature of Promotion)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q51", "number": 51, "question": "In the business world, acting ethically can often", "options": ["decrease feedback.", "increase suspicion.", "increase sales.", "decrease trust."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Increase sales. As the face of their companies, salespeople are responsible for building and maintaining these relationships. If clients know they can trust a salesperson (and, by extension, their company), they\u2019re more likely to keep buying, which leads to more sales. Acting ethically will help alleviate suspicion from customers and other competition as well as increase trust. Ethical actions don\u2019t always affect the level of feedback a salesperson or company receives. SOURCE: SE:106 Explain legal and ethical considerations in selling SOURCE: LAP-SE-106\u2014Keep It Real\u2014In Sales (Legal and Ethical Considerations in Selling)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q52", "number": 52, "question": "Which of the following are sources of an organization\u2019s internal data:", "options": ["Sales reports and business directories", "Sales invoices and cash register receipts", "Trade association reports and databases", "Customer records and government statistics"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Sales invoices and cash register receipts. Internal data are secondary data that already exist in the organization\u2019s own \u201cin-house\u201d information system. There are many sources of internal data, including sales invoices, cash register receipts, sales reports, expense accounts, customer records, and customer comments, to name a few. Business directories, government statistics, and trade association reports and databases are sources of an organization\u2019s external data\u2014secondary data that already exist outside the organization. SOURCE: IM:281 Describe options businesses use to obtain marketing research data (i.e., primary and secondary research) SOURCE: LAP-IM-281\u2014What's the Source? (Obtaining Marketing-Research Data)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q53", "number": 53, "question": "Which of the following is an objective a business might achieve through profit-oriented pricing:", "options": ["Creating an image for the business", "Being more competitive", "Increasing marketing share", "Maximizing profits"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Maximizing profits. Profit-oriented pricing is a category of pricing objectives that focuses on profit for the business. Some of the objectives a business might achieve through profit-oriented pricing include surviving, maximizing profits, earning a return on investment (ROI), and earning a return on sales. Creating an image for the business, being more competitive, and increasing marketing share are specific objectives a business might achieve by using sales-oriented pricing. Sales-oriented pricing focuses on increasing the total amount of income from sales. SOURCE: PI:002 Explain factors affecting pricing decisions SOURCE: LAP-PI-902\u2014Make Cents (Factors Affecting Selling Price)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q54", "number": 54, "question": "Which of the following is a question marketers who are focused on the product element of the marketing mix may ask themselves:", "options": ["Which messages should we send and which media should we use?", "Where should we make a product available?", "What level of quality should be produced?", "How can we bring in the necessary amount of income?"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "What level of quality should be produced? The marketing mix is a combination of the four elements of marketing\u2014product, price, place, and promotion. The product element refers to what goods, services, or ideas a business will offer its customers. To do this, marketers ask themselves questions like, \u201cWhat level of quality should be produced?\u201d or \u201cShould we offer one product or more than one product?\u201d \u201cHow can we bring in the necessary amount of income?\u201d is a question related to the price element of the marketing mix. \u201cWhere should we make a product available?\u201d is a question related to the place element. \u201cWhich messages should we send and which media should we use?\u201d is a question for the promotion element. SOURCE: MP:001 Explain the concept of marketing strategies SOURCE: LAP-MP-001\u2014Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q55", "number": 55, "question": "Moose Manufacturing learns one of its products doesn\u2019t meet safety standards, so it requests customers return, destroy, or stop using the product until they can resolve the issue. This is an example of which of the following:", "options": ["Planned obsolescence", "Voluntary recall", "Warning label", "Dishonest marketing"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Voluntary recall. Sometimes, companies are unaware of a potential product risk until the product is already on the market. In these cases, it is ethical for the company to issue a voluntary recall of the product\u2014removing it from the market and requesting that consumers return, destroy, or stop using the product\u2014until the issue can be resolved. Companies include warning labels on products to clearly inform customers about potential product risks. Dishonest marketing involves misleading information about products. Planned obsolescence is the practice of designing a product to become unusable before it should reasonably need replacement. SOURCE: PM:040 Explain business ethics in product/service management SOURCE: LAP-PM-040\u2014Safe and Sound (Ethics in Product/Service Management)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q56", "number": 56, "question": "Which of the following is an intangible product:", "options": ["A new set of tires", "Car transmission", "Car insurance", "A new coat of paint"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Car insurance. Car insurance is an intangible product because insurance cannot be perceived by the senses. Tires, car transmissions, and coats of paint are tangible products because they can all be seen and touched. SOURCE: SE:017 Explain the nature and scope of the selling function SOURCE: LAP-SE-017\u2014Sell Away (The Nature and Scope of Selling)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q57", "number": 57, "question": "If a company wants to increase brand awareness and drive potential customers to purchase, which of the following touchpoints would be most effective in a competitive market with a younger demographic:", "options": ["Traditional print advertising", "Direct mail campaigns", "Radio commercials", "Social media influencer partnerships"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Social media influencer partnerships. Touchpoints refer to all of the opportunities that businesses have to connect with customers and reinforce their brand value. For example, customers may find and connect with a business on its website, on social media, in a store, or in an advertisement, to name a few. If a company wants to increase brand awareness among a younger demographic and drive potential customers to purchase, social media influencer partnerships would be most effective. Direct mail campaigns, traditional print advertisements, and radio commercials would not be as effective with a younger demographic. SOURCE: PM:277 Identify customer touch points SOURCE: SurveyMonkey. (2024). How to identify and improve your customer touchpoints. Retrieved October 11, 2024, from https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/identify-customer-touchpoints"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q58", "number": 58, "question": "Which of the following best describes a product in the growth stage of a product life cycle:", "options": ["A car's sales decrease and sales begin to erode.", "A tablet's sales decrease and start to stabilize.", "A running shoe's profits are nonexistent.", "A cell phone's sales increase and costs decrease."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "A cell phone's sales increase and costs decrease. The product life cycle refers to the stages a product moves through from the time it is introduced to the market until the time it is taken off the market. The four stages of the product life cycle are introduction, growth, maturity, and decline. A cell phone's sales increasing and costs decreasing describes the growth stage. During the growth stage, a product quickly becomes established in the market. Profits improve as sales increase rapidly and costs go down. A running shoe's profits being nonexistent describes the introduction stage. A tablet's sales decreasing and starting to stabilize describes the maturity stage. A car's sales decreasing and sales beginning to erode describes the decline stage. SOURCE: PM:024 Identify the impact of product life cycles on marketing decisions SOURCE: LAP-PM-024\u2014Get a Life (Cycle) (Product Life Cycles)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q59", "number": 59, "question": "Dan is presenting to a room full of parents and begins by telling them a humorous story about the daily battle he has with his children to get them ready for school. What characteristic of an effective oral presentation is Dan demonstrating?", "options": ["Presenting a clear message", "Using impactful nonverbal communication", "Engaging and connecting with the audience", "Incorporating visual aids"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Engaging and connecting with the audience. By choosing to tell a relatable and humorous story about his children, Dan is demonstrating the ability to engage and connect with his audience. Dan does not make use of any visual aids (images, slideshows, charts, graphs, etc.). Dan is communicating with his audience by telling them a story which is a form of verbal communication. Dan\u2019s story does not present any clear message. SOURCE: CO:025 Make oral presentations SOURCE: LAP-CO-025\u2014Well Said! (Making Oral Presentations)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q60", "number": 60, "question": "To ethically manage project scope, Darius must ensure", "options": ["the project team doesn\u2019t take on unnecessary work.", "he checks with stakeholders throughout all phases of the project.", "the product meets or exceeds quality standards.", "the project team takes on as much work as possible."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "The project team doesn\u2019t take on unnecessary work. Scope management involves ensuring that a project stays within its defined boundaries and achieves all that it has agreed to do. It also means that the team does not attempt to take on too much and waste resources on unnecessary work. Checking with stakeholders throughout all phases of the project and ensuring the product meets or exceeds quality standards are examples of ethical management, but they do not fall under project scope. SOURCE: OP:675 Describe the role of ethics in project management SOURCE: LAP-OP-675\u2014Projects With Principles (Ethics in Project Management)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q61", "number": 61, "question": "Which of the following marketing careers involves dealing directly with consumers, managing customer complaints and feedback, and creating goodwill:", "options": ["Marketing management", "Customer service", "Product/Brand management", "Public relations"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Customer service. Customer service is a marketing career involving performing activities that increase customer satisfaction and create goodwill. Customer service professionals may answer customer questions, resolve complaints and returns, process orders, and perform many other duties that relate to customer satisfaction. Marketing management is a career area in which employees focus on all marketing functions, including channel management, marketing-information management, pricing, product/service management, promotion, and selling. Product/Brand management involves monitoring and developing one or more existing products or brands; planning the entire lifespan of a product or brand. Public relations is a career in which employees are responsible for establishing good relations between their business or organization and the public. SOURCE: PD:024 Explain employment opportunities in marketing SOURCE: LAP-PD-024\u2014Career Opportunities in Marketing"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q62", "number": 62, "question": "Which of the following scenarios best demonstrates exclusive dealing:", "options": ["A market is controlled by only one supplier.", "A retailer charges different customers different prices.", "A distributor only sells products from one producer.", "A store legally sells goods through unauthorized sales channels."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "A distributor only sells products from one producer. Exclusive dealing is a contractual agreement between a producer and a distributor where the distributor agrees to only sell the products of that specific producer. A monopoly is a type of market structure in which a market is controlled by one supplier, and there are no substitute goods or services readily available. Price discrimination is an illegal activity in which a business charges different customers different prices for the same product. The gray market refers to the legal sale of goods through unauthorized sales channels. SOURCE: CM:005 Explain legal considerations in channel management SOURCE: Federal Trade Commission. (n.d.). Exclusive dealing or requirements contracts. Retrieved September 17, 2024, from https://www.ftc.gov/advice-guidance/competition-guidance/guide-antitrust-laws/dealings-supply-chain/exclusive-dealing-or-requirements-contracts"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q63", "number": 63, "question": "An electronics company partners with an athletic wear company to create fitness trackers and workout apps targeted toward athletes and fitness fans. What type of marketing does this scenario describe?", "options": ["Ambush", "Affinity", "Mass", "Influencer"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Affinity. Affinity marketing is a type of marketing where a business forms a partnership with another company to provide goods or services and reach a new market. Because the electronics company is partnering with an athletic wear company and targeting the market of athletes and fitness aficionados, this is an example of affinity marketing. Mass marketing is designing products and directing marketing activities to appeal to the whole market. Ambush marketing is a promotional technique whereby a non-sponsoring business tries to associate with an event to gain recognition as a sponsor. Influencer marketing is a type of social media marketing in which businesses partner with popular social media users to promote their products and services. SOURCE: CM:021 Explain the nature of affinity partner relationships SOURCE: Hanna, K.T. (2024, May). Affinity marketing. Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://www.techtarget.com/whatis/definition/affinity-marketing"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q64", "number": 64, "question": "Starbucks creates separate product lines based on whether they are sold in coffee houses, grocery stores, or both. Starbucks is classifying its product lines according to", "options": ["customer group.", "product class.", "distribution method.", "price or quality."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Distribution method. Starbucks is classifying its products according to distribution method, or the outlets through which they are marketed. Product lines based on price or quality include products within the same price bracket or quality level. Product lines based on product class consist of products with similar characteristics or functions. Product lines based on customer group include products that appeal to a certain target market. SOURCE: PM:003 Explain the concept of product mix SOURCE: LAP-PM-003\u2014Mix and Match (The Nature of the Product Mix)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q65", "number": 65, "question": "A computer technology company conducts marketing research to estimate how much demand there will be for a new product it is developing. In this scenario, the company is conducting marketing research to __________ something.", "options": ["discover", "monitor", "explain", "predict"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Predict. Marketing research is the systematic gathering, recording, and analyzing of data about a specific issue, situation, or concern. Companies can conduct marketing research for several purposes, including to explain, predict, monitor, or discover something. Because the company in this scenario wants to know how much demand there will be for a new product it is developing, it is conducting marketing research to predict something. Marketing research can help them make accurate predictions about these and other marketing issues. The company is not conducting marketing research to explain, monitor, or discover something in this scenario. SOURCE: IM:284 Describe methods used to design marketing research studies (i.e., descriptive, exploratory, and causal) SOURCE: LAP-IM-284\u2014Better by Design (Marketing Research Designs)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q66", "number": 66, "question": "Latif decides to make the first and last questions of her questionnaire the most important because she knows that they will receive the most attention from respondents. Latif is being conscious of", "options": ["assimilation and contrast.", "priming and anchoring.", "primacy and recency.", "fatigue and drop-offs."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Primacy and recency. The primacy and recency bias theory says the first and last items will receive the most attention from an individual. Assimilation and contrast refer to the theory that a person\u2019s judgment of something can act as a type of anchor, influencing their later judgments. Fatigue and drop-offs occur when a respondent becomes tired, distracted, or disengaged. Priming and anchoring are when an early piece of information \u2018sets the tone\u2019 and limits or influences all the participant\u2019s subsequent answers. SOURCE: IM:293 Evaluate questionnaire design (e.g., types of questions, question wording, routing, sequencing, length, layout) SOURCE: Qualtrics. (2024). Survey question sequence, flow, & style. Retrieved October 2, 2024, from https://www.qualtrics.com/experience-management/research/question-sequence-flow-style/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q67", "number": 67, "question": "The marketing team for a clothing company considers what consumers want and are willing to pay when pricing their products. This best describes which of the following factors that impact pricing:", "options": ["Costs", "Government regulation", "Competition", "Supply and demand"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Supply and demand. When setting prices, marketers need to monitor business and economic conditions. Supply and demand are determined by what people want and what they\u2019re willing to pay. This scenario does not describe how competition, costs, or government regulation impact pricing. SOURCE: PI:015 Describe the role of business ethics in pricing SOURCE: LAP-PI-015\u2014Pricing With Purpose (Ethics in Pricing)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q68", "number": 68, "question": "Taco Bell and Doritos joined forces to increase their brand recognition. This is an example of", "options": ["brand positioning.", "brand extension.", "co-branding.", "brand licensing."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Co-branding. Companies that join forces to increase brand recognition, customer loyalty, and sales for the brands involved are co-branding. Brand positioning is trying to establish the \u201cpoint of difference\u201d factor that separates the brand from its competitors. Brand extension is when an existing brand name is used for a new or improved product line. Brand licensing allows one company to use another\u2019s brand name, brand mark, or trade character for a fee. SOURCE: PM:021 Explain the nature of product/service branding SOURCE: LAP-PM-021\u2014It's a Brand, Brand, Brand World! (Nature of Product Branding)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q69", "number": 69, "question": "Which of the following statements is true about brand values:", "options": ["They include both store brands and private brands.", "They are what a brand would be like if it were a person.", "They should be shared by everyone in the company.", "They are not important for consumers to know."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "They should be shared by everyone in the company. Brand values are the core of what the company believes in and cares about, so it makes sense that they\u2019re the biggest priority for companies developing their corporate brands. Successful corporate brands must take them to heart and be sure that everyone in the company\u2014from the CEO at the top to the retail employees at the bottom\u2014shares those values. When customers know a corporate brand\u2019s values, it is easier for them to develop relationships with the brand. A brand personality describes what a brand would be like if it were a person. Store brands and private brands are two types of distributor brands. SOURCE: PM:206 Explain the nature of corporate branding SOURCE: LAP-PM-206\u2014Corporate Identity (Nature of Corporate Branding)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q70", "number": 70, "question": "Which of the following is an example of complementary products:", "options": ["Smartphones and protective cases", "Cable TV and streaming services", "Books and e-readers", "Glasses and contact lenses"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Smartphones and protective cases. Complementary products are goods and/or services that are used together. Examples of complementary products include smartphones and protective cases, scarves and mittens, software and computers, and burger and fries. Books and e-readers, cable TV and streaming services, and glasses and contact lenses are each examples of substitute products. A substitute product is a product that takes the place of another product and satisfies the same need or want. SOURCE: PM:127 Identify methods/techniques to generate a product idea SOURCE: LAP-PM-127\u2014Unleash Your Mind (Techniques for Generating Product Ideas)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q71", "number": 71, "question": "Joel has been analyzing the sales data for his company's products and finds that customers are struggling to afford them at their current price points, leading to a decline in sales. He needs to adjust his pricing strategy while still ensuring the company remains profitable. What marketing mix element should Joel prioritize in his strategy to achieve these goals?", "options": ["Promotion", "Product", "Price", "Place"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Price. The price element requires marketers to determine the amount of money they will ask in exchange for their products. Because he needs to adjust his pricing strategy while still ensuring the company remains profitable, Joel should prioritize the price element of the marketing mix. The product element of the marketing mix refers to what goods, services, or ideas a business will offer its customers. The place element focuses on considerations in getting a selected product in the right place at the right time. The promotion element refers to the various types of communications that marketers use to inform, persuade, or remind customers of their products. SOURCE: CM:007 Coordinate channel management with other marketing activities SOURCE: Lake, L. (2021, January 6). What the marketing mix is and why it's important. Retrieved September 17, 2024, from https://www.liveabout.com/what-is-a-marketing-mix-2295520"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q72", "number": 72, "question": "A sales invoice can provide marketers with valuable data like", "options": ["the current product offerings of competing companies.", "key changes in the economy.", "current happenings in the industry.", "the amount of money customers have spent with their business."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "The amount of money customers have spent with their business. A sales invoice can tell marketers who a customer is, what industry they are in, how much money they have spent with the business, their preferred method of payment, and more. Data on the current product offerings of competing companies, key changes in the economy, and current happenings in the industry are not provided in a sales invoice. SOURCE: IM:012 Describe the need for marketing data SOURCE: LAP-IM-012\u2014Data Do It (Need for Marketing Data)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q73", "number": 73, "question": "If a customer is looking for a cutting-edge product with proprietary technology, a salesperson should emphasize the", "options": ["product\u2019s unique features.", "business\u2019s style.", "product\u2019s durability.", "product\u2019s style."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Product\u2019s unique features. A cutting-edge product likely possesses unique features that should be shared with a customer who is interested in such advantages. A customer who is interested in advanced technology or cutting-edge products is unlikely to be swayed by the aesthetics of a business or product. Product durability is not an inherently cutting-edge product. SOURCE: SE:109 Analyze product information to identify product features and benefits SOURCE: LAP-SE-109\u2014Find Features, Boost Benefits (Feature-Benefit Selling)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q74", "number": 74, "question": "An advertisement stating that a company\u2019s coffee is \u201caward-winning\u201d is", "options": ["making a claim.", "using a testimonial.", "giving features.", "showing uses."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Making a claim. Ad copy that purports to be award-winning makes a general or specific claim for the product. When features are discussed in an ad's copy, factual information about the product is given, such as the type of engine in a car. When product use is featured in ad copy, the ad tells readers how they can use the product. A testimonial is someone's personal statement about the benefits of the product. SOURCE: PR:014 Explain the components of advertisements SOURCE: ChefsBest. (2024). Ad claims 101: What every marketer needs to know. Retrieved October 15, 2024, from https://www.chefsbest.com/ad-claims-101-what-every-marketer-needs-to-know"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q75", "number": 75, "question": "Can an inanimate object be a sampling unit?", "options": ["No; sampling units are always individual people.", "Yes; a sampling unit is any individual element of a target population.", "Yes; sampling units are most frequently inanimate objects.", "No; a sampling unit must beable to respond in some way to stimuli."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Yes; a sampling unit is any individual element of a target population. After marketers have carefully identified their target population, they use sampling to choose a representative (or typical) group of units within that population from whom to obtain data for the research study. This group is called the sample. Sampling units are often, but not always, individual people. They could also be businesses, households, or entire towns\u2014they can even be plants, light bulbs, or other inanimate objects. SOURCE: IM:285 Discuss the nature of sampling plans (i.e., who, how many, how chosen) SOURCE: LAP-IM-285\u2014Take Your Pick (Nature of Sampling Plans)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q76", "number": 76, "question": "Which of the following is the first step in the marketing planning process:", "options": ["Creating a strategy", "Goal setting", "Implementing the plan", "Assessing your current situation"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Goal setting. Marketing plans are a key component of any successful business plan. The first step of the marketing planning process is objective and goal setting. This step is an opportunity to think big picture and set goals. The second step is to assess your current situation, followed by creating the plan and strategy. The final steps of the marketing planning process involve implementing the plan and managing it. SOURCE: MP:006 Explain the nature of marketing planning SOURCE: Udemy. (2020, February). The marketing planning process: Four steps to success. Retrieved September 19, 2024, from https://blog.udemy.com/marketing-planning-process"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q77", "number": 77, "question": "Ever since Grace was very young, she has wowed people with her paintings. Now a professional painter, Grace continues to impress. Grace has a(n) __________ for painting.", "options": ["mentor", "aptitude", "compassion", "loathing"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Aptitude. Aptitude refers to a natural ability to do something. In this case, Grace has an aptitude for painting because she possesses a natural ability that has wowed people since she was very young. Neither compassion (a feeling of sympathetic pity and concern), loathing (a feeling of intense disgust), nor mentor (an experienced and trusted advisor) applies to Grace's experience with painting. SOURCE: PD:023 Identify tentative occupational interest SOURCE: Indeed. (2024, November 28). What is aptitude? Definition and common tests. Retrieved January 23, 2025, from https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/career-development/what-is-aptitude"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q78", "number": 78, "question": "Which of the following is a benefit that technology has on the product/service management function:", "options": ["Employee satisfaction", "Cost increases", "Real-time monitoring", "Less automation"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Real-time monitoring. One benefit that technology has on the product/service management function is that it provides real-time monitoring. Technology allows businesses to track product performance, market trends, customer behavior, etc., in real time. This allows for improved decision-making and timely responses. Technology can help businesses increase efficiency and reduce costs through automation. Technology does not necessarily lead to employee satisfaction. SOURCE: PM:039 Describe the use of technology in the product/service management function SOURCE: Nathanson, B. (2023, May 15). Digital product management: What it is and how it can benefit your business. Retrieved October 9, 2024, from https://academy.broadcom.com/blog/valueops/what-is-digital-product-management-business-benefits"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q79", "number": 79, "question": "Felicity recognizes a need to make a purchase, conducts some rudimentary research on potential products to fill that need, and subsequently makes a purchase. Felicity\u2019s buying behavior would fall under the __________ theory of buying behavior.", "options": ["internal", "environmental", "generic", "cultural"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Generic. The generic theory of buying behavior is the most basic theory of buying behavior. It consists of simply recognizing a need and making a purchase to meet that need. The environmental theory of buying behavior explains how buyers exhibit different buying behavior based on their current situation or setting. The cultural theory of buying behavior explains how a person\u2019s values and beliefs are impacted by their community and how those values influence buying decisions. The internal theory of buying behavior emphasizes how personality traits and lifestyle impact a customer\u2019s buying behavior. SOURCE: SE:359 Discuss motivational theories that impact buying behavior SOURCE: Chron. (2021, July 20). Business theories of buying behavior. Retrieved September 23, 2024, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/business-theories-buying-behavior-13883.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q80", "number": 80, "question": "Which function of a marketing information system involves analyzing the facts and information gathered, then translating them into a more understandable, organized format?", "options": ["Data gathering", "Data processing", "Marketing research", "Information reporting"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Data processing. Data processing, which involves analyzing the data collected and putting them into formats useful to a business, is an important function of a marketing information system. Information reporting involves handling the flow of information within a business. The basic function of a marketing information system is to gather internal and external data important to the business on an ongoing, continuous basis. Marketing research is the systematic gathering, recording, and analyzing of data about a specific marketing problem or situation. SOURCE: IM:001 Explain the nature and scope of the marketing-information management function SOURCE: LAP-IM-001\u2014Get the Facts Straight (Marketing-Information Management)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q81", "number": 81, "question": "An example of applied research is", "options": ["investigating how the universe began.", "learning which areas in the world get the most precipitation.", "exploring how to make healthy meals on a limited budget.", "understanding the components that comprise DNA."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Exploring how to make healthy meals on a limited budget. Applied research studies particular circumstances to apply the information to real-life situations. It helps improve the human condition by finding practical solutions for existing problems like how to make healthy meals on a limited budget. Investigating how the universe began, understanding the components that comprise DNA, and learning which areas in the world get the most precipitation are examples of basic research. SOURCE: IM:292 Identify sources of error in a research project (e.g., response errors, interviewer errors, non-response errors, sample design) SOURCE: Dovetail. (2023, February 27). Basic vs. applied research: What\u2019s the difference? Retrieved October 2, 2024, from https://dovetail.com/research/basic-vs-applied-research/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q82", "number": 82, "question": "Companies provide the public information through", "options": ["discouraging natural monopolies.", "internal financial auditing.", "warehousing software.", "public relations activities."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Public relations activities. Public relations activities are ways of providing information to others. For example, press conferences and press releases are ways of providing information to the media in the hopes that the media will publish or broadcast the information so it is available to the general public. Warehousing software and internal financial audits provide relevant information to the business, but not the public. Natural monopolies do not impact how companies provide information to the public. SOURCE: PR:250 Explain communications channels used in public-relations activities SOURCE: Pride, W.M., & Ferrell, O.C. (2020). Marketing 2020 (20th ed.) [Lesson 17-5]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc."}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q83", "number": 83, "question": "Which of the following is an external audience for public relations activities:", "options": ["Suppliers", "Supervisors", "Executives", "Managers"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Suppliers. One of the main functions of a business's public relations activities is to reach external audiences, or those groups that are outside of the company. These groups include the local community, government officials, customers, suppliers, creditors, etc. A business\u2019s primary internal audience is employees, which includes managers, executives, and supervisors. SOURCE: PR:253 Discuss internal and external audiences for public-relations activities SOURCE: Finzelpr. (2022). External and internal public relations. Retrieved October 12, 2024, from https://finzelpr.com/external-and-internal-public-relations/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q84", "number": 84, "question": "Every day at 5:30 p.m., Grant refrains from checking his work email and spends the rest of the evening with his family. Grant\u2019s coworkers know to wait until the next day before bringing work to him. Which of the following techniques for balancing personal and professional responsibilities is Grant utilizing:", "options": ["Prioritizing and delegating", "Taking time off", "Assigning specific time blocks for different tasks", "Setting clear boundaries"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Setting clear boundaries. Grant is setting clear boundaries by sticking to specific work hours and refraining from checking his work email outside of those hours. Taking time off refers to taking personal leave time, which Grant has not done. Grant is not assigning specific time blocks for different tasks or prioritizing and delegating, which refers to creating a list of tasks, identifying the most important, and focusing on completing them first. SOURCE: PD:179 Balance personal and professional responsibilities SOURCE: Aurora. (2024, July 16). Balancing work and life: Achieving personal and professional harmony. Retrieved October 14, 2024, from https://auroratrainingadvantage.com/articles/balancing-work-and-life/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q85", "number": 85, "question": "Which of the following is a reason why customer voice is important in branding:", "options": ["It helps identify market trends and consumer preferences.", "It eliminates the need for branding strategies.", "It reduces the need for market research.", "It guarantees positive customer experiences."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "It helps identify market trends and consumer preferences. Customer voice is important in branding because it helps identify market trends and consumer preferences. Customer feedback directly reveals what customers are looking for, which allows brands to alter their offerings to meet customer expectations. While customer voice helps with market research, it does not eliminate the need for it. Customer voice can contribute to positive customer experiences, but it does not guarantee them. Customer voice does not eliminate the need for branding strategies. SOURCE: PM:276 Describe the role of customer voice in branding SOURCE: Vocalcom. (2024). Voice of the customer: The key to brand success. Retrieved October 14, 2024, from https://www.vocalcom.com/blog/voice-of-the-customer-the-key-to-brand-success"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q86", "number": 86, "question": "Laney can create a promotional mix for her new business by combining different forms of", "options": ["cash flow statements.", "job analyses.", "word-of-mouth advertising.", "marketing communication channels."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Marketing communication channels. A promotional mix is a combination of marketing communication channels that a business uses to send its messages to consumers (i.e., advertising, sales promotion, personal selling, and publicity). Job analyses are systematic studies of the tasks and responsibilities of a job and its place in an organization. Cash flow statements are financial summaries with estimates as to when, where, and how much money will flow into and out of a business. Word-of-mouth advertising is promotion and publicity for a business provided by customers who tell others of their satisfaction with the business. While word-of-mouth advertising can be a component of promotion, it is not an essential element to which Laney could combine different forms to create a comprehensive promotional mix. SOURCE: PR:003 Identify the elements of the promotional mix SOURCE: LAP-PR-903\u2014Spread the Word (Nature of the Promotional Mix)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q87", "number": 87, "question": "Which of the following is an example of specialty media:", "options": ["Coffee mug with a business\u2019s logo on it", "Billboard on the side of a building", "Someone holding a sign outside of a business", "Large poster in the lobby of a movie theater"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Coffee mug with a business\u2019s logo on it. A coffee mug with a business\u2019s logo on it is an example of specialty media. Specialty media is a type of \u201cother\u201d media that features a business\u2019s name or logo, is a useful item such as a baseball cap or a pen, and is given away freely. A large poster in the lobby of a movie theater is considered movie theater advertising, not specialty media. A billboard, also known as a poster panel, on the side of a building is an example of out-of-home media. Someone holding a sign outside of a business is an example of a human directional. SOURCE: PR:007 Explain types of advertising media SOURCE: LAP-PR-007\u2014Ad-quipping Your Business (Types of Advertising Media)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q88", "number": 88, "question": "Rather than first designing a new product and then developing a model, Jasper and Chaminda work together to design and build a prototype at the same time. Jasper and Chaminda are using which of the following quality-control methods:", "options": ["Process performance management", "Concurrent engineering", "Lean production", "Taguchi method"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Concurrent engineering. By working simultaneously, Jasper and Chaminda are implementing concurrent engineering. Concurrent (simultaneous) engineering refers to performing the various stages of product design and development at the same time, instead of one after another. This method enhances product quality by allowing potential problems to be caught and adjusted earlier in the development process. While lean production, the Taguchi method, and process performance management are common quality-control methods, they are not being implemented in this scenario. SOURCE: OP:163 Identify quality-control measures SOURCE: LAP-OP-163\u2014Take Control (Quality-Control Measures)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q89", "number": 89, "question": "An important economic freedom in the private enterprise system is", "options": ["competition.", "inflation.", "corruption.", "poverty."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Competition. Competition is an important characteristic of private enterprise. The freedom to compete is also an important economic freedom for individuals. If you are looking for a job, you are free to compete with other job seekers. If you own your own business, you can compete with similar businesses for customers. Freedom to compete allows you to market your assets to your best advantage. While corruption, inflation, and poverty all exist within the private enterprise system, they are not considered important economic freedoms. SOURCE: EC:009 Explain the concept of private enterprise SOURCE: LAP-EC-909\u2014People Power (The Private Enterprise System)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q90", "number": 90, "question": "Which of the following forms of technology enhances efficiency, adaptability, and security in accounting processes while fostering seamless collaboration across geographical barriers:", "options": ["Machine learning", "Robotic process automation", "Artificial intelligence", "Cloud-based infrastructure"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Cloud-based infrastructure. Cloud-based infrastructure refers to the hardware and software that make up cloud computing services. One of the key characteristics of cloud-based infrastructure is that it fosters seamless collaboration across geographical barriers, while enhancing efficiency, adaptability, and security in accounting. Machine learning (ML) is a form of technology that utilizes algorithms to create models capable of automatically processing extensive datasets. Robotic process automation (RPA) is a form of technology that automates rule-based tasks and eliminates manual data entry in companies. Artificial intelligence (AI) is used in accounting to automate and optimize numerous processes that were once repetitive, labor-intensive, and time-consuming. While machine learning, robotic process automation, and artificial intelligence are useful technologies in accounting, they do not foster seamless collaboration across geographic barriers. SOURCE: FI:352 Explain the use of technology in accounting SOURCE: Montgomery, J. (2021, July). Cloud infrastructure. Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://www.techtarget.com/searchcloudcomputing/definition/cloud-infrastructure"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q91", "number": 91, "question": "A shampoo producer pays a retailer monthly to ensure its products appear prominently on the store's shelves. Which of the following does this best describe:", "options": ["Exclusive territory", "Just-in-time inventory", "Slotting allowance", "Tying agreement"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Slotting allowance. A slotting allowance is a payment from a producer to a retailer to ensure its products appear on the store\u2019s shelves. A tying agreement is an illegal agreement requiring a customer to buy other products to obtain desired goods and services. Exclusive territories are designated areas or regions in which a distributor is required to only sell products from a specific producer. Just-in-time inventory is an inventory method in which goods are ordered so that they arrive when they are needed rather than being stockpiled. SOURCE: CM:006 Describe ethical considerations in channel management SOURCE: LAP-CM-006\u2014The Right Path (Ethics in Channel Management)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q92", "number": 92, "question": "A company is looking to come up with a new product idea. To do so, the marketing team schedules an hour-long meeting where the goal is to share as many different ideas as possible. This technique describes", "options": ["brainstorming.", "a focus group.", "a survey.", "brainwriting."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Brainstorming. Brainstorming is a creative-thinking technique often done in a group setting involving the identification of as many different ideas as possible during a certain time frame. Because the marketing team's goal is to share as many different ideas as possible during an hour-long meeting, this scenario best describes brainstorming. A focus group is a group formed for the purpose of discussing a specific topic. A survey is a marketing research method that involves asking consumers questions to learn their opinions and the reasons behind those opinions. Brainwriting is a brainstorming technique that involves writing random ideas or words on pieces of paper and then sharing them with others to build on each other\u2019s ideas. SOURCE: PM:128 Generate product ideas SOURCE: VanZandt, P. (2022, March 23). Brainstorming vs. brainwriting: Similarities and differences. Retrieved October 10, 2024, from https://ideascale.com/blog/brainstorming-vs-brainwriting"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q93", "number": 93, "question": "Millie wants to find a new sugar cookie recipe, but the search results show recipes for any cookie that contains sugar as an ingredient. What is the most efficient way Millie can narrow down her search?", "options": ["Choose a different search engine.", "Use hyphens to exclude different flavor cookies from her search.", "Select \u201cmore\u201d underneath the search bar, then \u201crecipes.\u201d", "Place quotation marks around \u201csugar cookies.\u201d"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Place quotation marks around \u201csugar cookies.\u201d Millie can narrow down her search results by placing quotation marks around the exact words she\u2019s looking for. Using hyphens to exclude a word from her search would help refine it, but it would not be the most efficient way, as Millie would have to exclude multiple flavors of cookies. The \u201cmore\u201d feature does not provide a \u201crecipes\u201d option. Choosing a different search engine would not resolve the issue because it resides in the broad nature of Millie\u2019s original search. SOURCE: NF:006 Demonstrate basic web-search skills SOURCE: GCFGlobal. (n.d.). Using search engines. Retrieved September 18, 2024, from https://edu.gcfglobal.org/en/internetbasics/using-search-engines/1/"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q94", "number": 94, "question": "Alec and Natalia politely settle their personal issues and return to work without holding grudges. Which benefit of open and honest communication are they experiencing?", "options": ["Better conflict resolution", "Increased sales", "Better ideas", "Encouraging questions"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Better conflict resolution. Disagreements, grudges, and hurt feelings take up time that could be used more efficiently. Transparent people face disagreements openly and politely. Alec and Natalia are not experiencing increased sales. While they may work more efficiently together and have better ideas, it is not a direct outcome in this scenario. Encouraging questions is a characteristic of open and honest communication, not a benefit. SOURCE: EI:129 Foster open, honest communication SOURCE: LAP-EI-129\u2014Can We Talk? (Fostering Open, Honest Communication)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q95", "number": 95, "question": "Corey is working as part of a team but consistently misses his assigned deadlines. Which trait of a good team member is Corey failing to demonstrate?", "options": ["Adaptability", "Sensitivity", "Mobility", "Reliability"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Reliability. Good team members can be counted on to go above and beyond expectations. It is difficult to work with someone who is unpredictable or who cannot be trusted to complete their assigned work on time. Good team members always meet deadlines, attend all meetings, participate enthusiastically, and perform quality work that exceeds the standards put forth by the team. Adaptability is the ability to adjust to changing conditions. Mobility is the ability to move freely. Sensitivity is the ability to be aware of and responsive to the feelings of others. SOURCE: EI:045 Participate as a team member SOURCE: LAP-EI-045\u2014Team Up (Participating as a Team Member)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q96", "number": 96, "question": "Which of the following is an example of product placement:", "options": ["A celebrity is shown drinking a new soda flavor in a commercial.", "A popular movie shows a character drinking a new soda flavor.", "A new soda flavor is priced cheaper than similar products.", "A new soda flavor is advertised on social media platforms."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "A popular movie shows a character drinking a new soda flavor. Product placement is a sales-promotion strategy in which a product or brand is mentioned or used as a prop by types of media such as TV, film, or the theater. Advertising on social media is an example of digital marketing. A commercial is a televised advertisement. A celebrity using the product is a celebrity endorsement. Pricing a new soda flavor cheaper than similar products is a pricing decision and is not product placement. SOURCE: PR:249 Identify communications channels used in sales promotion SOURCE: Shopify. (2023, July 12). How does product placement work? Examples and benefits. Retrieved October 17, 2024, from https://www.shopify.com/blog/product-placement"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q97", "number": 97, "question": "Brett likes small talk, but he makes sure to keep this to a minimum when speaking with his supervisor because that is their preference. This is an example of adapting to", "options": ["an emergency.", "unfamiliar conditions.", "resource issues.", "personal interactions."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": "Personal interactions. Every individual has a different style of interaction, and to be successful, you must adapt your behavior to suit them. Some clients enjoy small talk, while others just want to get down to business. When Brett alters his communication style to match his supervisor\u2019s preference, he adapts the personal interaction. This is not an example of resource issues, an emergency, or unfamiliar conditions. SOURCE: EI:006 Demonstrate adaptability SOURCE: LAP-EI-006\u2014Go With the Flow (Demonstrating Adaptability)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q98", "number": 98, "question": "Sabrina lends money to a bank for two years. However, she cannot access the money before the end of the two years without paying a penalty. What type of lending investment did Sabrina use?", "options": ["Money market account", "Certificate of deposit", "Savings account", "Bond"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": "Certificate of deposit. In this scenario, Sabrina is using a certificate of deposit (CD), or a lending investment in which you lend money to a bank at a set interest rate for a particular period of time. With CDs, you are guaranteed a certain rate of return, but you can\u2019t access your money before the end of the time period without paying a penalty. By giving up the right to use your money for a period of time, you can earn a higher return than with a savings or money market account. Savings accounts allow you to lend money to a bank for the benefit of being able to access it at pretty much any time. A bond allows individuals to lend money to a government, municipality, or corporation to earn a set rate of interest for a specified time period. Unlike CDs, you don\u2019t pay a penalty if you withdraw the invested amount from a bond before the end of the time frame. A money market account allows individuals to lend money to a bank to earn interest but includes key rules and restrictions, such as a minimum balance requirement or being charged a monthly fee if you don\u2019t meet the account minimum. SOURCE: FI:077 Explain types of investments SOURCE: LAP-FI-077\u2014Invest for Success (Types of Investments)"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q99", "number": 99, "question": "Gigi\u2019s store is flourishing except for one specific product she is struggling to sell. Which product bundle is most likely to solve Gigi\u2019s issue:", "options": ["New product bundle", "Mix-and-match bundle", "Inventory clearance bundle", "Pure bundle"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": "Inventory clearance bundle. Gigi is most likely to resolve her issue by creating an inventory clearance bundle and pairing the product she is struggling to sell with one of her faster moving ones at a discounted price. Shoppers who are interested in the faster moving product will then see the bundle as a bargain and be more inclined to buy it. A mix-and-match bundle is better for businesses attempting to sell multiple, similar, fast-moving products. A new product bundle is wise for businesses promoting a new product. A pure bundle is appropriate for businesses that do not want to sell certain products individually. SOURCE: PM:041 Describe the nature of product bundling SOURCE: Kesavan, S. (2024, May 13). Product bundling strategy, advantages & examples. Retrieved October 9, 2024, from https://www.zoho.com/inventory/academy/order-fulfillment/what-is-product-bundling.html"}, {"id": "u-e094e3f1-q100", "number": 100, "question": "Which of the following is a type of service policy:", "options": ["Delivery policy", "Pricing policy", "Liability policy", "Credit policy AAM - Apparel and Accessories Marketing Series Event ASM - Automotive Services Marketing Series Event BSM - Business Services Marketing Series Event BTDM - Buying and Merchandising Team Decision Making Event FMS - Food Marketing Series Event IMCE - Integrated Marketing Campaign \u2013Event IMCP - Integrated Marketing Campaign \u2013Product IMCS - Integrated Marketing Campaign \u2013Service MCS - Marketing Communications Series Event MTDM - Marketing Management Team Decision Making Event PSE - Professional Selling Event RMS - Retail Merchandising Series Event SEM - Sports and Entertainment Marketing Series Event STDM - Sports and Entertainment Marketing Team Decision Making Event specialist levels. Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio (dba MBA Research ). Each individual test item contained herein is the"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": "Delivery policy. Service policies are designed to govern the support a company provides to customers after the sale. Types of service policies include return and adjustment policies, delivery policies, installation policies, guarantee policies, and repair and maintenance policies. Pricing policies, credit policies, and liability policies are types of terms-of-sale policies, which focus on the aspects of a sale with which customers are most concerned. SOURCE: SE:932 Explain company selling policies SOURCE: LAP-SE-932\u2014Sell Right (Selling Policies)"}], "question_count": 100}, "u-26c361ff": {"id": "u-26c361ff", "name": "2019.pdf", "description": "", "questions": [{"id": "u-26c361ff-q1", "number": 1, "question": "A business that effectively coordinates channel management with marketing activities is more likely to provide", "options": ["good customer service.", "attractive product displays.", "free delivery.", "flexible credit terms."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Good customer service. Channel management is one of the marketing functions that must work with the other marketing activities to get goods and services from producers to consumers. The goal of marketing is to satisfy consumer wants and needs while achieving company goals. Businesses cannot satisfy those needs and provide quality customer service unless all the marketing activities work togethe r. For example, businesses are only able to serve customers when they have the advertised items on hand and at the right price. Not all businesses need or use product displays, provide free del ivery, or offer flexible credit terms. SOURCE: CM:007 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 22-23). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q2", "number": 2, "question": "Which of the following types of business organizations reduces or limits the risk of its stock holders:", "options": ["Franchise", "Sole proprietorship", "Corporation", "Partnership"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Corporation. A corporation, which is owned by its stockholders, limits the losses or risk s to the amount each individual owner has invested in the corporation. The other types of business organization s are not owned by stockholders. A partnership usually divides the risk among two or three partners. I n a sole proprietorship, the owner generally assumes all of the risk. A franchise is a contractual agreemen t between a parent company and a franchisee to distribute goods and services. SOURCE: BL:003 SOURCE: LAP- BL-001\u2014Own It Your Way (Types of Business Ownership)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q3", "number": 3, "question": "Which of the following would probably use a longer channel of distribution than th e others:", "options": ["A bag of oranges", "A printing press", "An airplane", "A bottle of shampoo"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " A bottle of shampoo. Shampoo is a low-cost, standard product that would probably use a longer channel of distribution than the other alternatives. A bag of oranges is perishable and needs to us e short channels. A printing press is highly technical, requires installation, and is quite heavy ; therefore, it would rely on short channels. An airplane is technical and quite heavy and would probably use a direct route from the producer to the industrial user. SOURCE: CM:003 SOURCE: LAP- CM-003\u2014Channel It (Channels of Distribution)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q4", "number": 4, "question": "Electronic billing, purchase-order verification, bar-code technology, and image pro cessing are examples of", "options": ["functions of the finance department.", "horizontal channel integration.", "integrated data between channel members.", "vertical channel integration."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Integrated data between channel members. The technology of electronic billing, purcha se-order verification, bar coding, and image processing enable channel members to integrate data. Vertical and horizontal channel integration are methods of organizing distribution channels. The finance department may utilize the methods to share data, but the methods are not unique to that department. SOURCE: CM:004 SOURCE: Ingram, D. (2017, November 21). Channel management techniques. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/channel-management-techniques-3072.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q5", "number": 5, "question": "When filing a tort against a business, the plaintiff must establish that the defendan t", "options": ["violated the doctrine of sovereign immunity.", "damaged property intentionally.", "conspired with a competitor.", "breached the duty of care."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Breached the duty of care. The duty of care is the basic principle that expects all individu als and businesses to exhibit socially responsible behavior by using caution to prevent ha rm and by watching out for one another. A tort is a private wrongdoing that potentially harms another person or entity. If a business or one of its employees breaches the duty of care, the business may be held liable for the tort. However, the plaintiff must have grounds or proof that establishes that the business or its employee (defendant) has committed a wrongful act, thereby breaching the duty of care. Intentional dam age and conspiring with a competitor (collusion) are types of torts. The doctrine of sovereign immuni ty is the universally accepted principle that each nation has the right to manage its own government and d evelop its own laws. SOURCE: BL:069 SOURCE: Gordon, J.M. (n.d.). Breach of duty of care. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://thebusinessprofessor.com/knowledge-base/breach- of-duty- of-care/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q6", "number": 6, "question": "A producer can minimize channel conflict among its distributors and retailers by", "options": ["selling its items directly to the end users.", "offering different products through each channel.", "establishing slotting fees for certain channels.", "requesting that the channel members carry only its brand."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Offering different products through each channel. Channel conflict can occur when channel mem bers are competing among themselves for customers. When each channel sells different products, they are not directly competing among themselves for business. For example, if a guitar manufacturer sells its lin e of guitars through authorized distributors and sells accessories for the guitars through online retai lers, the channel members are not competing for the customers because they are selling different products. Bypassing channel members and selling directly to end users, establishing slotting f ees, and requesting channel members to carry only its brand are actions that tend to create channel conflict rath er than minimize it. SOURCE: CM:008 SOURCE: Perner, L. (1999-2018). Channel management and conflict. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://www.consumerpsychologist.com/dist_Channel_Management.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q7", "number": 7, "question": "What is an advantage of verbal communication?", "options": ["You use passive listening skills to understand the message.", "Tone of voice can be used to express emotions and thoughts.", "It focuses attention on facial expressions rather than words to express enthusiasm.", "People must see you to understand the intent of your message."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Tone of voice can be used to express emotions and thoughts. This means that people can show their interest and enthusiasm by what they say and by the way they say it. Although body l anguage conveys intent, people can communicate how they feel through their choice of words. The words that people use often express their interest and enthusiasm. A key element of verbal communication is active l istening. SOURCE: CO:147 SOURCE: The Business Communication. (2013-2018). Advantages and disadvantages or oral communication. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://thebusinesscommunication.com/advantages-and-disadvantages- of-oral- communication/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q8", "number": 8, "question": "When Amber walked by Ryan's desk, she noticed that Ryan was raking his left hand th rough his hair, that his face was red, and that he kept hitting the enter button on his keyboard with his right ha nd, while frowning at his computer screen. Based on his nonverbal cues, Amber would probably assume t hat Ryan was", "options": ["patient.", "frustrated.", "bored.", "enthusiastic."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Frustrated. Nonverbal cues can tell others a lot about your emotions. In this situation, Ryan's nonverbal behavior indicated that he was frustrated because he couldn't get his computer to do what he wanted it to do. If Ryan was patient, he would not continuously hit his keyboard, turn red, or frown. If Ryan was bored, he would be inattentive about his situation or surroundings. He might even yawn or do someth ing other than computer work for a while. Enthusiasm is associated with a positive attitude. SOURCE: CO:059 SOURCE: Mind Tools Content Team. (1996-2018). Body language. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.mindtools.com/pages/article/Body_Language.htm"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q9", "number": 9, "question": "You're giving directions to a group of coworkers, and you want to be sure they do exactly what you say. You should", "options": ["raise your voice.", "give directions in the proper order.", "make the directions challenging.", "demonstrate the final steps of the directions."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Give directions in the proper order. It's much easier for your listeners to follow along if you giv e directions in the order in which they should be completed. Raising your voice isn't necessary when giving directions; in fact, it may intimidate your listeners. Your directions should not be ch allenging, even if the task itself is challenging. If you choose to demonstrate how to complete the directions, yo u should show how to do each step, not just the final ones. SOURCE: CO:083 SOURCE: Karten, N. (2014, December 1). How to give instructions so that people will follow them. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.techwell.com/techwell- insights/2014/12/how-give-instructions- so-people-will-follow-them"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q10", "number": 10, "question": "It is most appropriate for businesspeople to use complex, technical jargon when they are", "options": ["speaking with coworkers.", "greeting new customers.", "introducing a friend to a business associate.", "informally conversing with an acquaintance."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Speaking with coworkers. Jargon is a specialized language known only to a certain group of pe ople. Industries and companies often use jargon that is meaningful to their businesses and may not be easil y understood by people outside their industries or companies. Coworkers are more likely to use jargon because they are familiar with the terms and their meanings or applications. New customers, fri ends, business associates, and acquaintances may not be familiar with a specific industry's jargon . SOURCE: CO:084 SOURCE: Your Dictionary. (2018). Examples of jargon. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://examples.yourdictionary.com/examples- of-jargon.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q11", "number": 11, "question": "The human resources manager sends an email to all employees stating that they will need to park on the street on Tuesday because the maintenance department will be repairing the company's parking lot. This is an example of a(n)", "options": ["informational message.", "projection report.", "business proposal.", "formal inquiry."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Informational message. Communicating information involves providing others with facts . In the example, the human resources manager is informing the company's employees about an issue with t he company's parking lot. The human resources manager is not writing a projection report, business proposal, or form al inquiry. SOURCE: CO:039 SOURCE: Roberts, S.J. (2012). Fundamentals of business communication (pp. 219-225). Tinley Park, IL: The Goodheart-Willcox Company."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q12", "number": 12, "question": "A memorandum is typically used for communication that takes place", "options": ["within a business.", "among competitors.", "infrequently.", "between friends."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Within a business. Memorandums are a frequently used form of brief, written communication excha nged by people within an organization. Memorandums are rarely used among competitors or between friends. SOURCE: CO:094 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (p. 203). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q13", "number": 13, "question": "Jayson just learned his company wants to hire a new public relations assis tant. He posts the job position information on his personal social media accounts and gives contact information for the manager that will be conducting interviews. Why is this inappropriate use of social media?", "options": ["It could give Jayson's friends an unfair advantage over other job candidates.", "It is unprofessional to post company employment information on a personal site.", "Jayson is using inside knowledge to appear more important on his social sites.", "Jayson is using his company's image to increase his number of social contacts."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " It is unprofessional to post company employment information on a personal site. Jayson 's placement of a job opening on his personal sites is unprofessional and gives the company little control over the presentation or distribution of the information. There's no indication his friends would gain a n unfair advantage over other candidates since Jayson is not conducting the interviews. It's not clear whether Jayson is trying to look important or increase his social contacts; however, those acts are of less concern than the unprofessionalism of posting employment information. SOURCE: CO:206 SOURCE: Arens, W.F., Weigold, M.F., & Arens, C. (2013). Contemporary advertising (14th ed.) [pp. 530-532]. New York: McGraw-Hill/Irwin."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q14", "number": 14, "question": "Which of the following is a common product-related complaint:", "options": ["Pressure selling", "Reduced price", "Poor service", "Incorrect size"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Incorrect size. Customers' complaints about products are the result of defective, damaged, or spoiled products; the wrong size or color; mispricing; or the failure to meet the customers' needs. Poor service and the use of pressure in selling cause complaints about the sales staff. Customers seldom complain about reduced prices. SOURCE: CR:010 SOURCE: LAP- CR-010\u2014Righting Wrongs (Handling Customer Complaints)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q15", "number": 15, "question": "Two similar brand promises may be carried out differently depending on their", "options": ["business environments.", "types of packaging.", "logos.", "slogans."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Business environments. Two similar brand promises may be carried out differently dep ending on their business environments. For example, a product that is sold in stores will have different touchpoi nts than a product that is sold online. Types of packaging, logos, and slogans should not have a si gnificant impact on how a brand promise is carried out. SOURCE: CR:001 SOURCE: LAP- CR-006\u2014Share the Promise (Identifying Brand Promise)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q16", "number": 16, "question": "A company decides to spend $5,000 on new office furniture instead of putting that money toward the marketing budget. What is the opportunity cost of this decision?", "options": ["Lost benefits of additional marketing", "Office furniture", "$5,000", "Lost benefits of new furniture"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Lost benefits of additional marketing. When a choice is made about the best use of resou rces, the next- best alternative that is given up is called the opportunity cost of that choice. Opportunity cos t is the benefit that is lost when you decide to use scarce resources for one purpose rather than for another. The opportunity cost of the company's decisions is the lost benefits from additional mar keting. Office furniture, $5,000, and lost benefits of new furniture are not considered opportunity costs in this situation. SOURCE: EC:001 SOURCE: LAP- EC-006\u2014Are You Satisfied? (Economics and Economic Activities)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q17", "number": 17, "question": "Businesses that carry a considerable assortment of goods but only one or a few related produ ct lines are __________ businesses.", "options": ["specialty", "discount", "service", "limited-line"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Limited-line. Limited-line businesses specialize in the products that they off er for sale. They usually carry an excellent assortment of those goods. Service businesses perform intangible activities that satisfy the wants of consumers or industrial users. Specialty businesses typically carry a very l imited variety of products. Discount businesses sell products at reduced prices and usually carry a variety of item s. SOURCE: EC:070 SOURCE: LAP- EC-070\u2014Business Connections (Business and Society)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q18", "number": 18, "question": "Which of the following is a true statement about how technology affects the external busines s environment:", "options": ["Technology is the main way to compete with other businesses.", "Not all businesses are affected by technology.", "Businesses must look for updated technology all the time.", "Certain target markets do not use technological products."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Businesses must look for updated technology all the time. Because new technology is being i ntroduced all the time, businesses must constantly be on the lookout for updated technological tools that will help them to be more efficient. All businesses are affected by technology in one way or another. Techn ology is just one way for a business to compete \u2014it might also compete through pricing strategies, promotional campaigns, etc. Though some target markets may use technology more than others, all target mark ets are affected by and use technology. SOURCE: EC:105 SOURCE: LAP- EC-105\u2014What's Shakin'? (Factors Affecting the Business Environment)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q19", "number": 19, "question": "Business ethics involve considering issues about what is", "options": ["legal and illegal.", "right and wrong.", "safe and unsafe.", "positive and negative."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Right and wrong. Ethics are the basic principles that govern an individual's behavior. In busin ess, ethics involves how a business behaves in its dealing with other businesses, customers, and employ ees. Businesses consider issues about what is right and wrong when they decide how to op erate and how to treat others. To be ethical, they need to consider how their actions affect the welfare of ot hers. It is a matter of considering what is the right way to act and what is the wrong way to act. It does not invo lve considering what is legal or illegal, although some actions that are unethical are also ill egal. Business ethics does not involve considering issues about what is safe and unsafe, or what is posi tive and negative. SOURCE: EC:106 SOURCE: LAP- EC-106\u2014On the Up and Up (Business Ethics)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q20", "number": 20, "question": "Legal protection of an invention or a process granted by the government to its owners for a certain number of years is a", "options": ["license.", "patent.", "trademark."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Patent. A patent is one form of government protection of private property. Other government protection works granted by government and giving their creators sole rights to them for 28 years. A trademark i s an exclusive name or symbol that is placed on a product and may be registered with the government to prevent its use by others. A license is official permission to do or own a specified thin g. SOURCE: EC:008 SOURCE: LAP- EC-016\u2014Regulate and Protect (Government and Business)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q21", "number": 21, "question": "A depression is characterized by which of the followin g:", "options": ["Fewer bankruptcies", "Increased consumer spending", "Rapidly rising GDP", "High unemployment"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " High unemployment. A depression is an economic decline that lasts longer than a recess ion. The characteristics of a depression are a rapidly falling GDP and high unemployment that, in turn, r esult in a decline in consumer spending and an increase in bankruptcies. SOURCE: EC:017 SOURCE: LAP- EC-001\u2014Measure Up? (Gross Domestic Product)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q22", "number": 22, "question": "Interest rates rising and falling by a wide range on a regular basis often are an indication of", "options": ["price equilibrium.", "seasonal unemployment.", "flexible capital.", "economic instability."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Economic instability. Interest rate is the percentage figure used in calculating interest char ges. The interest is the price of borrowing money. Interest rates rising and falling by a wide range on a regular basis often is an indication of economic instability. The interest rate has an effect on the a mount of money available to loan and the amount that businesses and individuals are willing to borr ow. For example, when rates are high, borrowing decreases because the price of borrowing is high. This te nds to slow down the economy. In a stable economy, interest rates remain fairly constant and fluctuate by only a few percentage points. Interest rates rising and falling by a wide range on a regular basis is no t an indication of seasonal unemployment, flexible capital, or price equilibrium. SOURCE: EC:084 SOURCE: Heakal, R. (2018, January 17). Forces behind interest rates. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/insights/forces-behind-interest-rates/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q23", "number": 23, "question": "George thinks his culture is superior to all other cultures. This is known as", "options": ["collectivism.", "ethnocentrism.", "stereotyping.", "individualism."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Ethnocentrism. Thinking your culture is superior to others is known as ethnocentrism. Collec tivism refers to a society that is integrated into strong groups. Stereotyping is generalizing others based on their cultural backgrounds. Individualism refers to a society in which group ties are loose, an d everyone is expected to take care of him/herself. SOURCE: EC:045 SOURCE: LAP- EC-045\u2014On Top of the World (Impact of Culture on Global Trade)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q24", "number": 24, "question": "When your level of self-esteem is low, this causes you to have", "options": ["confidence in your ability.", "difficulty with visualization.", "doubts about yourself.", "appreciation of life."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Doubts about yourself. When self-doubts are present, self-esteem has dropped. These doubts and your low level of self-esteem may keep you from having confidence in your own abi lity or an appreciation for life. A low level of self-esteem does not necessarily cause difficulty with visualiz ation \u2014the practice of imagining yourself in possession of a present or desired strength. Visualization is a method of overcoming low levels of self-esteem. SOURCE: EI:016 SOURCE: Kimbrell, G. (2012). Succeeding in the world of work (p. 127). Columbus, OH: McGraw-Hill Education."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q25", "number": 25, "question": "Thinking of a time when you were happy and proud can help you", "options": ["find gaps between your behavior and values.", "avoid activities that do not make you happy.", "determine what values made you feel that way.", "accept others' feedback regarding your values."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Determine what values made you feel that way. Thinking about times in your life when you were happy or proud, or certain experiences that stand out in your mind as meaningful, can help you determine the values that made those times so significant. Thinking of a time when you were happy and pr oud does not necessarily help you completely avoid activities that do not make you happy. It also does not nec essarily help you find gaps between your behavior and values or accept others' feedback regarding yo ur values. SOURCE: EI:126 SOURCE: LAP- EI-126\u2014Assess Yourself (Assessing Your Personal Behavior and Values)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q26", "number": 26, "question": "Adhering to an established set of personal ethics is referred to as", "options": ["deceit.", "integrity.", "honest y.", "truth."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Integrity. Your integrity involves the overall quality of your moral character. Honesty refers to truthfulness, fairness, and authenticity. Truth is an indisputable or accepted fact. The practice of che ating, misleading, or misrepresenting is known as deceit. SOURCE: EI:022 SOURCE: LAP- EI-138\u2014Sincerely Yours (Demonstrating Honesty and Integrity)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q27", "number": 27, "question": "Ethical dilemmas should be thought of as", "options": ["challenges.", "opportunities.", "easily avoidable.", "emergencies."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Opportunities. It's important to remember that each ethical dilemma you encounter is an op portunity to make the right decision and show that you can follow ethical principles. So, it's a g ood idea to view ethical dilemmas not as challenges, but as opportunities. Ethical dilemmas are encountered often and are not easily avoidable. They should not be viewed as emergencies. SOURCE: EI:124 SOURCE: LAP- EI-124\u2014What's the Situation? (Reasons for Ethical Dilemmas)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q28", "number": 28, "question": "Jamie is constantly running from obligation to obligation, without a second of free time, and feels like he is behind on all of his work. Jamie is most likely to be", "options": ["a procrastinator.", "a perfectionist.", "bad at time management.", "overcommitted."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Overcommitted. Being overcommitted means committing to more than what is possible, necessar y, or desirable. People who are overcommitted, like Jamie, have countless obligations, events, and tas ks each day. There is no indication that Jamie is a perfectionist, bad at time management, or a procras tinator, though these could all be potential causes of his overcommitment. SOURCE: EI:077 SOURCE: LAP- EI-077\u2014Commit to It! (Managing Commitments in a Timely Manner)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q29", "number": 29, "question": "Which of the following might be considered a violation of employees' privacy in the w orkplace:", "options": ["Use of time clocks", "Use of video cameras", "Use of security guards", "Use of computer passwords"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Use of video cameras. Some businesses, such as retail establishments, use video cameras to monitor customers and prevent shoplifting. If these cameras are focused on employees, it might be considere d a violation of the employees' privacy. Businesses that use video cameras should inform employee s so they are aware that their actions are being recorded and monitored. Also, the business has an obligation not to use cameras in areas that are designed specifically for employees, such as break rooms. The use of time clocks is a method of recording time on the job rather than a violation of privacy. The us e of security guards is a safety factor that benefits employees and customers. The use of computer passwords provides employees with a certain amount of privacy by allowing them to protect their compu ter systems from unauthorized access. SOURCE: EI:029 SOURCE: Guerin, L. (2011, October 10). Workplace cameras and surveillance: Rules for employers. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/workplace- cameras-surveillance-employer-rules-35730.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q30", "number": 30, "question": "Integrity is one of the most important traits for ethical leaders to develop because it", "options": ["is the foundation for other ethical principles.", "builds consistency in difficult situations.", "ensures they will avoid ethical dilemmas.", "challenges leaders to be more confident."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Is the foundation for other ethical principles. Integrity means adhering to an established set of personal ethics and sound moral principles. Integrity is perhaps the most important trait that an ethical leader can have because it is the foundation for many other principles, including respect, fairness, trustworth iness, and altruism. Integrity leads to positive relationships, loyalty, and stability. Integr ity does not necessarily build consistency in difficult situations, ensure that leaders will avoid ethical dilem mas, or challenge leaders to be more confident. SOURCE: EI:131 SOURCE: LAP- EI-131\u2014Be the Change (Nature of Ethical Leadership)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q31", "number": 31, "question": "What often increases when a person continually resists change or fails to adapt to new ci rcumstances?", "options": ["Inability to use logic", "Feelings of contentment", "Sense of accomplishment", "Levels of stress"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Levels of stress. Stress is a mental, physical, or emotional feeling of pressure or tension. Adap tability is the ability to adjust or modify attitudes and/or behavior to new situations or circumstances. Whe n people are not willing to adapt to new situations, they often feel higher levels of stress. Fighting or ignoring new circumstances can increase stress, which can harm a person's health and well-being. Resisti ng change does not necessarily affect an individual's ability to reason or use logic. When a person learns how to adapt to change, s/he may feel content or a sense of accomplishment by accepting the change. B eing adaptable often helps a person to relax, which can facilitate creative thinking and learning. SOURCE: EI:006 SOURCE: LAP- EI-023\u2014Go With the Flow (Demonstrating Adaptability)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q32", "number": 32, "question": "What is the first step in the process of leading change?", "options": ["Show why the change is necessary.", "Communicate the change to everyone involved.", "Ask others to join you in leading the change.", "Put the change into action."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Show why the change is necessary. Showing why the change is necessary is the f irst step in the process of leading change. After you've proven the need for the change, you can ask others to join you i n leading it, communicate the change to everyone involved, and put the change into action. SOURCE: EI:005 SOURCE: LAP- EI-022\u2014Start the Revolution (Leading Change)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q33", "number": 33, "question": "Being enthusiastic about your job is an example of what type of behavior that builds pos itive working relationships?", "options": ["Having a good attitude", "Getting to know others on your work team", "Demonstrating courtesy and respect", "Being cooperative"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Having a good attitude. Being enthusiastic about your job is an example of having a good attitude in the process of building positive working relationships. A positive attitude on the job means many things, including being enthusiastic, being optimistic and cheerful, and refusing to grumble or c omplain. Being enthusiastic is not an example of getting to know others on your work team or being cooperativ e. It may go along with demonstrating courtesy and respect, but it is best as an example of having a good a ttitude. SOURCE: EI:037 SOURCE: LAP- EI-037\u2014Can You Relate? (Fostering Positive Working Relationships)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q34", "number": 34, "question": "Companies spend lots of time and money developing positive organizational cultures bec ause positive culture is linked with", "options": ["company failure.", "stock market increases.", "employee turnover.", "improved results."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Improved results. Companies spend a lot of time and money developing positive workplace cultures because positive culture is linked with improved results, such as employee satisfaction, i ncreased productivity, high morale, and unity among diverse employees. Positive culture is not linked to s tock market increases, employee turnover, or company failure. SOURCE: EI:064 SOURCE: LAP- EI-064\u2014Culture Club (The Nature of Organizational Culture)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q35", "number": 35, "question": "The entrepreneurs best equipped to work long hours and overcome obstacles are ones who possess", "options": ["financial knowledge.", "passion for their work.", "technological skills.", "confidence."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Passion for their work. Entrepreneurs who are passionate about their work find it easier to work the lon g hours required. They are also more likely to overcome obstacles out of a desire to continue do ing what they love. Confidence can help an entrepreneur overcome challenges, but it does not necessarily help him/her work long hours. Financial knowledge can help an entrepreneur overcome financial obstacles, but it may not help an entrepreneur solve other problems or deal with long work hours. Technological skills are very useful in solving some problems, but they don't help an entrepreneur person ally work for long periods of time. SOURCE: EN:040 SOURCE: Gregory, A. (2018, May 20). 10 character traits of successful small business owners. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.thebalancesmb.com/successful-owners- character-traits-2951855"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q36", "number": 36, "question": "Each pay period, Kendra has her employer automatically deposit her paycheck in to her checking account so the funds are available for use when she needs them. In this situation, money is functi oning as a(n)", "options": ["form of cash.", "unit of measure.", "medium of exchange .", "store of value."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Store of value. Money functions as a store of value when it is saved rather than spent. The money can be held over time, and it retains value for future purchasing power. Money serves as a unit of measure when it is used to express the value or worth of something. Money serves as a medium of exchange when it is used to obtain goods and services. Cash is a form of money \u2014currency and coins. Because Kendra's paycheck was automatically deposited in her bank account, currency and coins have not be en touched. SOURCE: FI:060 SOURCE: Clark, B., Basteri, C.G., Gassen, C., & Walker, M. (2014). Marketing dynamics (3rd ed.) [p. 45]. Tinley Park, IL: The Goodheart-Willcox Co."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q37", "number": 37, "question": "Bryant recently applied for a personal loan from the Maryville Community Credit Unio n, but his application was rejected. Bryant has a friend who works at the credit union, so he asks her wha t went wrong with his application. She told Bryant that the credit union's manager is prejudi ced and rarely accepts applications from individuals of Bryant's religion. The credit union vio lated Bryant's right to", "options": ["equal credit opportunity.", "a guaranteed credit line.", "proper notice of rejection.", "practice his religion."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Equal credit opportunity. All individuals are entitled to receive equal opportunity for cr edit under consumer credit protection laws. This means that creditors may not discriminate against an individual because of his/her race, color, religion, national origin, sex, marital status, or age when they make cred it decisions. Individuals are not entitled to a credit guarantee. Methods of notifying candidates of their rejection for credit lines vary, and there is not a single \u201cproper\u201d way that is considered appropriate . Maryville Credit Union discriminated against Bryant because of his religion, but it did not violate his right to practice his religion. SOURCE: FI:002 SOURCE: Irby, L. (2018, April 21). Consumer credit laws you should be familiar with . Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.thebalance.com/consumer-credit-laws-you- should- be-familiar-with-4068374"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q38", "number": 38, "question": "Saving the money that you might ordinarily spend each day on a cup of coffee and a donut", "options": ["is the sacrifice you must make for future financial security.", "will not result in significant savings.", "can help you achieve larger financial goals.", "is not a practical step in reaching your financial goals."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Can help you achieve larger financial goals. Making purposeful spending decisions, instea d of spending out of habit or impulsively, is an important step in achieving larger financial goals . Even small daily savings add up to significant amounts over time. Day- to-day spending does not have to be sacrificed entirely for future financial security, as long as you're aware of your spending and are making purposeful decisions. Small savings every day are a very practical step in reaching your financial goals. SOURCE: FI:065 SOURCE: Benve, R. (2018, August 14). How to set SMART personal financial goals. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://toughnickel.com/personal-finance/How- to-Set-Personal- Financial-Goals-Budgeting"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q39", "number": 39, "question": "Sasha's personal budget contains two broad categories for her expenses. She should put her mortgage, her car insurance payment, and her utilities in the __________ expenses category.", "options": ["variable", "fixed", "net", "gross"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Fixed. When you make a personal budget, it's important to divide your expenses into two broad categories. Fixed expenses are those that stay the same from month to month, like mortgages, car insurance payments, and utilities. Variable expenses change from month to month. Net and gross are terms that are used to describe income, not expenses. SOURCE: FI:066 SOURCE: Inc. (2018, April 19). Fixed and variable expenses. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://www.inc.com/encyclopedia/fixed-and-variable-expenses.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q40", "number": 40, "question": "The following is written on the back of a check: \u201cFor deposit only; Maria Evans; Acc ount #285655.\u201d This is an example of a(n) __________ endorsement.", "options": ["restrictive", "genera l", "open", "congruent"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Restrictive. Banks require checks to be endorsed before processing. Endorsement involves signi ng the back of the check, which allows the funds to be transferred from the check source to the paye e. There are different types of endorsements. A restrictive endorsement limits how the check can be processed. In the example, the check can only be deposited to the endorser's (Maria) specified account. The c heck cannot be cashed or placed into another account. A general endorsement allows the endorser to cash the check or deposit it into the account of his/her choice \u2014there are no restrictions placed on the funds transfer. Open and congruent endorsements are fictitious terms. SOURCE: FI:560 SOURCE: Pritchard, J. (2018, August 2). See how to endorse checks. When and how to sign. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.thebalance.com/how- to-endorse-checks-315300"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q41", "number": 41, "question": "Which of the following is the most likely action that the government takes when a person miss es the deadline for filing his/her income tax return:", "options": ["Allowance", "Refund", "Extension", "Penalty"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Penalty. A penalty is a punishment. The government depends on income tax to support public pro grams. When people do not provide income tax information when it is needed, the government often imposes a penalty, usually a fine or fee. Ongoing failure to report income can result in imprisonment. The government does not offer a refund or allowance for missing an important deadline. However, a pers on can file for an extension to avoid being penalized for missing a filing deadline. SOURCE: FI:074 SOURCE: IRS. (2014, April 18). Tips for taxpayers who missed the tax deadline. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.irs.gov/newsroom/tips-for-taxpayers-who-missed- the-tax-deadline"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q42", "number": 42, "question": "Income from sales, cost of goods sold, gross profit on sales, operating expenses, and net profit or loss are all part of a(n)", "options": ["sales budget.", "balance sheet.", "income statement.", "marketing plan."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Income statement. An income statement is a financial summary that shows how much money the business has made or lost. It is also called a profit- and-loss statement. A balance sheet shows a firm's assets, liabilities, and owner's equity. A marketing plan is a set of procedures or strategies for attracti ng the target customer to the business. A sales budget is an estimate of expenditures related to sales. SOURCE: FI:094 SOURCE: LAP- FI-004\u2014Watch Your Bottom Line (Income Statements)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q43", "number": 43, "question": "Lucia, a business owner, just hired a new employee. What is one thing she should be s ure to do on the employee's first day?", "options": ["Provide the new employee with all the details of every project s/he will be working on.", "Start the new employee on work right away so that s/he becomes accustomed to his/her job duties.", "Assign the new employee a mentor who can answer any questions s/he may have.", "Let the employee work on trivial tasks for a few days so that s/he can ease into working."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Assign the new employee a mentor who can answer any questions s/he may have. One sim ple way to make an employee feel comfortable is to assign a mentor. The mentor doesn't need to be the employee's direct supervisor \u2014it just needs to be someone who can show the new employee the ropes. It will help the new employee to have one ready-made friend who can show her/him around. Lucia should pr ovide some sort of orientation for the new employee before s/he starts working. There are many important things the employee will need to know about the company's policies and his/her benefits. Al though it is important to make sure the employee has information about the projects s/he is working on, Lucia won't want to overwhelm the new employee with too much information on the first day. It's also important not to give the employee busy work that doesn't fit into his/her job description. After all, that's not why the employee was hired, and this won't help the new employee become more comfortable at work. SOURCE: HR:360 SOURCE: Moon, L. (2018, January 16). New employee onboarding: A success template for every hire. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://blog.trello.com/new-employee-onboarding-best- practices-for- new-hires"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q44", "number": 44, "question": "What does a business need in order to understand why a successful product i s suddenly losing popularity?", "options": ["Purchasing documents", "Sales records", "Secondary data", "Marketing information"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Marketing information. Marketing information is all of the marketing-related data available ins ide and outside the business. This includes information about customers, competitors, demographics, etc. Businesses need marketing information in order to understand why a product that has been successful is suddenly losing popularity. For example, marketing information might tell a business that the targ et market for the product is decreasing in size because of age, or that a competitor has introduced a simil ar product that sells for less. Once the business understands the reason for the loss in popularity, it can take steps to correct the problem. Sales records are a type of marketing information, but they usually indicate only the decrease in sales rather than the reason for the decrease. Secondary da ta is a type of marketing information that has been collected for purposes other than the project at hand. It may not be useful in determining why a product is now losing popularity. Purchasing documents are documents a business uses to purchase goods and services. SOURCE: IM:012 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 654-656). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q45", "number": 45, "question": "Which of the following describes an ethical privacy policy:", "options": ["It includes automatically sending email promotions to customers.", "It puts the interests of the company over those of the customer.", "It includes a system to protect customers in the event of a data breach.", "It tries to hide information about data collection processes."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " It includes a system to protect customers in the event of a data breach. An ethical privacy policy puts t he customers first. Part of putting the customers first is securely protecting customer data and having a plan in place if a data breach does occur. Putting the interests of the company ahead of those of the cust omer is generally not ethical. Automatically sending email promotions to customers is not necessaril y part of an ethical privacy policy. Hiding information about data collection processes is unethical . SOURCE: IM:025 SOURCE: LAP- IM-025\u2014Info With Integrity (Ethics in Marketing-Information Management)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q46", "number": 46, "question": "Which of the following is a technology tool that allows a business to observe a custom er's Internet activities:", "options": ["Hyperlink", "Cookie", "Spam", "Host"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Cookie. Cookies are text files that a business puts on a website visitor's computer hard drive. The text files allow the business to observe or track the visitor's Internet behavior and retrieve inform ation during subsequent visits to its website. Cookies provide the business with information about a par ticular customer's browsing behavior, buying patterns, and preferences. A hyperlink is a component of an electronic document that an Internet user can click on, allowing him/her to jump to another place wit hin the document or to jump into a different document. Spam is junk email. A host stores web pages on a server for a monthly fee. SOURCE: IM:183 SOURCE: Target Internet. (2018). Digital marketing guide to cookies. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.targetinternet.com/digital-marketing-guide- to-cookies/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q47", "number": 47, "question": "The Henry Smith Company wants to select a representative group of consumers to survey. What part of marketing research is it doing?", "options": ["Experimentation", "Observation", "Analyzing", "Sampling"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Sampling. The process of choosing a representative group of consumers to survey is samplin g. It is usually impossible to study everyone, so researchers must use sampling. Observation gathers data, experimentation tests cause and effect, and analyzing interprets the data. They are all i mportant to marketing research but are not part of sampling. SOURCE: IM:010 SOURCE: LAP- IM-010\u2014Seek and Find (Marketing Research)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q48", "number": 48, "question": "Managers and researchers have formalized their decisions into a statement of what the marketing research study will achieve, known as a", "options": ["research problem.", "relevant variable.", "decision problem.", "research objective."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Research objective. Research objectives are formal statements of what a marketing research study will achieve. Relevant variables are the types of information studied in a marketing research projec t (e.g., brand awareness, customer satisfaction, etc.). A decision problem is the issue from the managers' perspective. A research problem is the issue from the researchers' perspective. SOURCE: IM:282 SOURCE: LAP- IM-282\u2014What's the Problem? (Marketing Research Problems)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q49", "number": 49, "question": "The data needed for sales volume analyses and market share analyses come from", "options": ["sales invoices.", "expense reports.", "company sales reports.", "customer records."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Company sales reports. The data needed for sales volume analyses and market share analyses come from the facts and figures in sales reports. Expense reports let a company know how much mone y is being spent on employees' food, lodging, travel, etc. Sales invoices don't show sales i n relation to goals, budgets, prior time periods, etc. Customer records don't include sales data for the entire company. SOURCE: IM:184 SOURCE: LAP- IM-184\u2014Data Diving (Identifying Marketing Data)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q50", "number": 50, "question": "Orson, a researcher, is asking a customer a series of questions during a scheduled meeting. Or son is using the __________ method to collect marketing data.", "options": ["observation", "relational", "interview", "contact"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Interview. Researchers often collect marketing data by conducting interviews with customers. The interviews can take place over the telephone, through the computer, or by holding face- to-face discussions (group or individual). An interview is a good method to use when the busin ess wants in-depth information from the respondents. The disadvantage to holding interviews is the expense. Observ ation is a research method that involves watching customers. Relational and contact interviews are fictiti ous terms. SOURCE: IM:289 SOURCE: Zikmund, W.G., & Babin, B. (2010). Essentials of marketing research (4th ed.) [pp. 156-158]. Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q51", "number": 51, "question": "What is an indirect, mechanical-observation data-collection method that a business can use to obtain accurate information about the specific types of products that its customers are buying?", "options": ["Point- of-sale scanners", "Comment cards", "Manual equipment", "Sound-wave meters"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Point- of-sale scanners. Many businesses use data from their point- of-sale devices (computerized cash registers) to collect marketing information. Because the point- of-sale scanner records all of the customers' purchases, a business can use the device to (indirectly) \u201cobserve\u201d its customers' purchas ing habits on an ongoing basis. The business can use the data to determine its fast-moving items and its customers' brand preferences. Comment cards are small, short, preprinted questionnaires. Manual equipment is too broad a term to specifically address how marketing researchers coll ect data. Marketing researchers do not use sound-wave meters to collect information about the types of products th at customers are buying. SOURCE: IM:418 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 373-379). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q52", "number": 52, "question": "The following appeared on a recent survey: \"Do you agree that the government wastes taxpayers' money by supporting unnecessary programs?\" This is an example of a(n)", "options": ["open -ended inquiry.", "indifferent statement.", "leading question.", "unstated alternative."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Leading question. Leading questions tend to influence the respondents' answers and create bias, whi ch skews results. Because words such as \"wastes\" and \"unnecessary programs\" tend to generate str ong emotional reactions and overall negative views about the topic, the survey question is biased. The question is a closed-ended question because it requires a \"yes\" or \"no\" answer. The situat ion does not exemplify an indifferent statement, an open-ended inquiry, or an unstated alternative. SOURCE: IM:293 SOURCE: Churchill, G.A., Brown, T.J., & Suter, T.A. (2010). Basic marketing research (7th ed.) [pp. 302-303]. Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q53", "number": 53, "question": "Which marketing function helps businesses answer questions like, \u201cWho are our customers?\u201d and \u201cWhere are they located?\u201d", "options": ["Pricing", "Product/Service management", "Marketing-information management", "Promotion"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Marketing-information management. Marketing-information management involves gathering, accessin g, synthesizing, evaluating, and disseminating information. If the information is accurate, it can help businesses answer questions like, \u201cWho are our customers?\u201d and \u201cWhere are they located?\u201d Product/Service management involves deciding on the products that a business will produc e or offer. Pricing focuses on determining and adjusting prices to maximize return and meet customers' percep tions of value. It involves paying attention to supply and demand, as well as the prices that com petitors are charging. The promotion function communicates information about goods, services, images, and/or ideas to achieve a desire outcome. Promotion informs, persuades, or reminds customers about a busines s and/or its products through methods such as advertising, publicity, and sales promotion. SOURCE: MK:002 SOURCE: LAP- MK-001\u2014Work the Big Seven (Marketing Functions)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q54", "number": 54, "question": "Would a successful business ever change its marketing strategy?", "options": ["No, once a business has a workable strategy, it should always be used.", "Yes, a business should have no more than two marketing strategies.", "No, changing marketing strategies is a complicated process.", "Yes, changes in the marketplace require changes in marketing strategy."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Yes, changes in the marketplace require changes in marketing strategy. Changes such as price increases, new competition, or an increase in operating expenses require that business es have flexible strategies. A responsible business operation will be prepared to redesign its strategies as neede d. SOURCE: MP:001 SOURCE: LAP- MP-002\u2014Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q55", "number": 55, "question": "Businesses need to identify their markets in order to", "options": ["improve their research methods.", "control the costs of production.", "reach goals and satisfy customers.", "be sure to appeal to all consumers."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Reach goals and satisfy customers. When businesses identify their target markets, they can plan their marketing activities in such a way that they can satisfy customers at the same time they are m eeting their own goals. Mass marketing, rather than target marketing, tries to appeal to all consumers. Market segmentation increases the costs of production, but it has benefited both large and small companies by making the most efficient use of resources. The improvement of marketing-research methods do es not depend on knowing a target market. SOURCE: MP:003 SOURCE: LAP- MP-003\u2014Have We Met? (Market Identification)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q56", "number": 56, "question": "For which of the following can a sales forecast predict sales:", "options": ["A specific geographic area", "The marginal utility", "A situation analysis", "The jury of executive opinion"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " A specific geographic area. Sales forecasts are defined as predictions of what a firm's sales w ill be during a specific future time period using a certain marketing plan. In addition to being able to pr edict sales for a specific geographic area, businesses can forecast sales for a specific product, an en tire line of products, a target market, and the firm's total market. The jury of executive (expert) opinion is a qualitative method of forecasting sales in which the executives of a company are asked to assess projected sales. A situation analysis is the determination of a firm's current business s ituation and the direction in which the business is headed. Marginal utility is defined as the incr ease in total usefulness that can be obtained by consuming or purchasing one additional unit of a product. SOURCE: MP:013 SOURCE: LAP- MP-005\u2014Futurecast (The Nature of Sales Forecasts)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q57", "number": 57, "question": "The Microsoft Corporation generated $51.12 billion in revenue in 2007. This is an example of", "options": ["factual information.", "unwarranted criticism.", "inconclusive evidence.", "current data."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Factual information. Facts contain true data or information. Microsoft has multiple sources of documentation that indicates it generated $51.12 billion in revenue in 2007, which make s the statement a fact. It is important for companies to verify facts when they are making business decisions. Basing decisions on incorrect information can be very costly to a company. Unwarranted critici sm is inappropriate, biased, or exaggerated feedback. Inconclusive evidence means that the presented f acts do not indicate a distinct or unquestionable outcome of a situation. The amount of money Micros oft generated occurred a few years ago; therefore, the statement does not contain current data. SOURCE: NF:077 SOURCE: Gunsch, J., Gilchrist, J., & Harris, B. (2018, September 7). What is the difference between fact and opinion? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://www.wisegeek.com/what- is-the- difference-between-fact- and-opinion.htm"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q58", "number": 58, "question": "Rhonda is doing research for a paper in her business class. She should use sources that", "options": ["were written by authors who are reputable.", "emotionally present one side of an issue.", "are no more than 20 years old.", "could be considered propaganda."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Were written by authors who are reputable. When evaluating a source, it's important to make sure that the author is reputable, credible, and respected. Sources that are emotional instead of objective sho uld be avoided. Propaganda is not considered a reputable source. Sources that are no more than 20 ye ars old may or may not be reliable, depending on the subject. SOURCE: NF:079 SOURCE: Purdue Online Writing Lab. (1995-2018). Evaluation during reading . Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://owl.purdue.edu/owl/research_and_citation/conducting_research/evaluating_sources_ of_information/evaluation_during_reading.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q59", "number": 59, "question": "Which of the following is a way in which technology has changed the way businesses operate:", "options": ["Productivity has decreased, and costs have increased.", "Employees are sometimesable to do their work from home.", "Entering new and foreign markets has become more complex.", "The nature of marketing has remained relatively the same."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Employees are sometimes able to do their work from home. The nature of work has changed due to the increase in telecommuting (working from home or a remote location) opportunities. The Internet and remote networking give many employees the ability to do their jobs without ever steppi ng foot into the office. Technology has actually helped productivity increase, not decrease, and co sts are lower. Technology makes entering new and foreign markets easier. The nature of marketing has changed because of technological innovations. SOURCE: NF:003 SOURCE: LAP- NF-004\u2014TECH-tastic (Technology's Impact on Business)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q60", "number": 60, "question": "The set of computer programs that manages the hardware and software of a computer is the", "options": ["digital connection.", "operating system.", "transfer protocol.", "electronic resource."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Operating system. The operating system manages the hardware and software and makes the computer work. The system connects the software to the hardware and controls the overall operation of the computer. The set of computer programs that manages the hardware and software of a computer is not the digital connection, the transfer protocol, or the electronic resource. SOURCE: NF:085 SOURCE: Goodwill Community Foundation, Inc. (1998-2018). What is an operating system? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://edu.gcfglobal.org/en/computerbasics/understanding- operating-systems/1/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q61", "number": 61, "question": "When developing a computer-based presentation, it is important that each slide contain", "options": ["creative transitions.", "colorful graphics.", "numerical data.", "key points."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Key points. Employees use presentation software to develop computer-operated visual aids tha t support an oral presentation. Slides for the presentation should include key points that highlight or reinforc e the most important information, which may or may not include numerical data. Colorful graphics and creativ e transitions often make a presentation more interesting, but they are not necessary elements for each slide. SOURCE: NF:008 SOURCE: Phillips, D.J.P. (2014, April 14). How to avoid death by PowerPoint [Video]. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Iwpi1Lm6dFo"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q62", "number": 62, "question": "Dmitri is building a new website. Which of the following does he need to register to o btain a web address for his new site:", "options": ["Web host", "Domain name", "Site builder", "Street address"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Domain name. The domain name that Dmitri registers will be the unique address of his new website. A web host allows a website owner to make his/her site accessible via the Internet. A s ite-builder is a program including templates and software to create the layout and design of a website. Web addresses are usually picked based on a company name or other important identifier, rather than the compa ny's street address. SOURCE: NF:042 SOURCE: The Grue. (2015, November 5). How to create a website \u2014a simple guide for beginners . Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://thegrue.org/how- to-create-a-website/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q63", "number": 63, "question": "Which of the following helps in the interpretation of mined data:", "options": ["Spreadsheets", "Databases", "Visual representation", "Clustering"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Visual representation. Once data has been mined, it is helpful to view it in a visual format so that it can be better understood. Visual tools are more easily understood than spreadsheets. Databases are the systems in which the information is stored. Clustering is a way to analyze data, but it does no t necessarily aid in interpretation of data. SOURCE: NF:152 SOURCE: Greiner, L. (2011, January 7). What is data analysis and data mining? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/Trends- and-Applications/What- is-Data- Analysis- and-Data-Mining-73503.aspx"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q64", "number": 64, "question": "The purpose of a company's operations function is to manage its", "options": ["day- to-day activities.", "long-term goals.", "communications.", "employees."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Day- to-day activities. Operations management is the process of planning, controlling, and monitoring th e day-to-day activities required for the company to function. This includes obtaining and allocating the appropriate type and amount of resources to do the work, such as employees, equipment, and supplies. Strategic management involves determining, monitoring, and managing long-term goals for the compa ny. Communication is the exchange of information, which is necessary in the workplace to complete a wide range of internal and external business activities. SOURCE: OP:189 SOURCE: LAP- OP-189\u2014Smooth Operations (Nature of Operations)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q65", "number": 65, "question": "Jason is an IT professional for his company, and one of his responsibilities involves th e maintenance of the office's copy machines. One of the company's old copiers is due for a replacement in a few we eks. What should Jason do to ensure that any sensitive information stored on the copier is protected?", "options": ["Jason does not need to do anything; the copier's manufacturer will handle the removal and/or overwriting of the hard drive.", "Remove or overwrite the copier's hard drive himself to make sure all information is protected.", "Contact the copier's manufacturer, dealer, or servicer to learn about options for removing or overwriting the copier's hard drive.", "Delete all the files and print jobs that appear on the copier screen under \"Recent.\""], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Contact the copier's manufacturer, dealer, or servicer to learn about options for removing or overwriting the copier's hard drive. Different manufacturers offer different services for the removal and protection of hard drives; some may remove it and return it to you to keep or overwrite on your own, whi le others may remove and overwrite the hard drive for you for an additional fee. Removing a hard drive on your own is risky\u2014it often requires special equipment and software, and it can be difficult to locate the drive. It i s better to work with a skilled technician who is trained for the task. You should always take some a ction toward protecting the information stored on your copier \u2014you should not leave such an important process in the hands of the manufacturer who does not know your company's wishes. Communicate with t hem to find out exactly what you need, or don't need, to do. Simply deleting files on a hard drive is not al ways permanent. Files can be retrieved or restored through other software, so it is important that you take further action such as overwriting the hard drive. SOURCE: OP:064 SOURCE: Federal Trade Commission. (2017, July). Digital copier data security: A guide for businesses. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business- center/guidance/digital-copier- data-security-guide-businesses"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q66", "number": 66, "question": "Which of the following is a true statement about the benefit of having a safe workplace:", "options": ["Financial expense is increased.", "Bodily injuries are decreased.", "Insurance claims are increased.", "Productivity is decreased."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Bodily injuries are decreased. A safe workplace reduces the possibility of additional financial expense and bodily injury. Because employees miss fewer workdays, productivity is increased. Insurance claims are increased when a workplace is considered risky because of a high rate of worker accidents or injuries. SOURCE: OP:007 SOURCE: Leonard, K. (2018, June 30). Importance of workplace health and safety. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/importance-workplace-health- safety-4973.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q67", "number": 67, "question": "A project is officially authorized to begin by the", "options": ["project charter.", "registration documents.", "Initiation Papers.", "statement of work."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Project charter. A project is officially authorized to begin by the project charter, an offici al document that is similar to (but more formal than) the statement of work. Registration documents and Initiation Papers are not common documents used in project management. SOURCE: OP:158 SOURCE: L AP-OP-158\u2014Projected To Win (Nature of Project Management)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q68", "number": 68, "question": "Before selecting the right people to work on a project, it is important to identify the", "options": ["required supplies.", "tangible resources.", "needed skills.", "physical facilities."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Needed skills. You know you need people to work on a project. Before you can identify the righ t people, you need to decide what skills are needed. For example, do you need people to use hand tools or lif t heavy boxes? Once you determine the needed skills, you can select people who have those skills and are willing to participate. Tangible resources are the supplies, equipment, and materials nee ded to complete a project as well as the physical facilities that might be needed. SOURCE: OP:003 SOURCE: LAP- OP-531\u2014Get What You Need (Identifying Project Resources)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q69", "number": 69, "question": "Superior Office Company received a state contract to supply office equipment to all public s chools in the area. What does the company need in order to effectively produce the contract?", "options": ["Products", "Outputs", "Supplies", "Inputs"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Inputs. Inputs are all of the economic resources used in producing goods and services. Inputs are human, natural, and capital resources. In order to produce the contract, Superior Office needs workers, equipment to sell, and the means to deliver the product to the schools. Supplies are industrial goods used in the operation of a business. Outputs are the goods and services produced as the result of combining inputs. Products are goods and services. SOURCE: OP:017 SOURCE: LAP- OP-017\u2014Can You Make It? (Nature of Production)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q70", "number": 70, "question": "Which of the following quality-control methods improves quality by saving time and allowing potential problems to be caught earlier in the product design and development process:", "options": ["Concurrent engineering", "House of quality matrix", "Lean production", "Pareto"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Concurrent engineering. Concurrent engineering is a quality-control method in which produ ct design and development are performed simultaneously. This saves time and allows potential problems or f laws to be caught earlier in the process. House of quality matrix is a quality-control tool that helps man agers to determine if a product meets customer needs or not. Lean production focuses on maximizing customer value while minimizing waste. A Pareto chart is a type of bar graph that helps identify wh ich problems need to be addressed first. SOURCE: OP:163 SOURCE: LAP- OP-008\u2014Take Control (Quality-Control Measures)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q71", "number": 71, "question": "One of the benefits of setting goals that will help you in your relationships with other s is that setting goals", "options": ["helps you stay on task.", "gives you a way to measure your progress.", "helps you understand yourself.", "raises your level of self-esteem."], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Helps you understand yourself. Goal setting helps you understand yourself, and understanding yourself helps you understand other people. Goal setting helps you stay on task, raises your level of self-esteem, and gives you a way to measure your progress, but these benefits do not necessarily help yo u in your relationships. SOURCE: PD:018 SOURCE: LAP- PD-016\u2014Go for the Goal (Goal Setting)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q72", "number": 72, "question": "A government enacts a law requiring all businesses to allow each employee a 15-minute break every four hours. This is an example of a law addressing an employee's right to", "options": ["workplace supervision.", "fair treatment.", "form unions.", "avoid harassment."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Fair treatment. Although regulation varies by country, labor laws are designed to protect workers f rom unfair labor and wage practices. By instituting a law that requires all businesses t o give all employees a break from their duties, the law is requiring that each employee receive the same or fai r treatment. Workplace supervision refers to the direction an employee receives to perform certain work- related tasks. Laws related to employee breaks do not affect the workers' rights to form unions. Harassment in the workplace generally refers to gender and race discrimination issues. SOURCE: PD:021 SOURCE: FindLaw. (2018) . Employees rights 101. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://employment.findlaw.com/employment-discrimination/employees-rights-10 1.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q73", "number": 73, "question": "Which of the following should you do when preparing your letter of application:", "options": ["Proofread quickly so you can send the letter sooner.", "Write a letter that is at least one page long.", "Repeat everything that is on your r\u00e9sum\u00e9 .", "Mention any mutual contacts you have."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Mention any mutual contacts you have. If you can, you should name someone you and the read er of your application letter both know. Of course, this isn't always possible, but it's a great way to get att ention. Your letter should not be more than a page long. You shouldn't repeat everything that's on your r\u00e9 sum\u00e9 ; your letter of application is intended to tell the reader things that aren't necessarily on the r\u00e9sum \u00e9. You should always proofread carefully, not quickly. Your letter of application is often the fi rst impression a company gets of you, so you want it to be perfect. SOURCE: PD:030 SOURCE: Adams, Susan. (2011). How to write a cover letter . Retrieved on September 10, 2018, from http://www.forbes.com/sites/susanadams/2011/03/24/how- to-write-a-cover-letter/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q74", "number": 74, "question": "One reason it is important for marketing professionals to follow ethical standards is to", "options": ["build positive relationships with other individuals and businesses.", "remove the risk of uncontrolled competition in the marketplace.", "improve working conditions and financial security.", "prevent unnecessary changes in the business environment."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Build positive relationships with other individuals and businesses. Ethical standards are gui delines for behavior. Because personal ethics among people vary, some industries develop ethical stand ards so that each person working in the industry knows what is acceptable and not acceptable behavi or in the profession. Businesses and employees who follow these standards demonstrate integrity and build trust with customers, other organizations, and community members. The primary purpose of followi ng ethical standards in marketing is not to remove competition from the marketplace, improve working cond itions and financial security, or prevent changes in the business environment. SOURCE: PD:137 SOURCE: Hill, B. (2018, June 29). The advantages of ethical behavior in business . Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/advantages-ethical-behavior- business-21067.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q75", "number": 75, "question": "A basic reason for the formation of a trade association is to", "options": ["provide information for consumers.", "find solutions for common problems.", "promote goodwill for an industry.", "establish a long-term group."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Find solutions for common problems. A trade association's members can collectively find so lutions to common problems that they might have difficulty handling as individuals. The me mbers also can share their knowledge and work together to increase the profitability of all members' business es. Trade associations are formed and disbanded according to the changing needs of the members. Some trade associations may promote goodwill or educate consumers, but those are not basic purposes of their formation. SOURCE: PD:036 SOURCE: Meyer, P. (2018, March 1). Why do people and companies join trade associations? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.comptia.org/about- us/newsroom/blog/comptia-blog/2018/03/01/why- do-people- and-companies-join-trade- associations"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q76", "number": 76, "question": "Which of the following is a common consequence for violating rules of conduct:", "options": ["Increased compensation", "Promotion", "Written warning", "Criminal charges"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Written warning. A written warning includes details about your infraction and information about any fut ure consequences that you could receive if the offense is repeated. It is commonly used as a con sequence when someone has violated a rule of conduct. Promotions are not consequences and would not be t he response to a rule violation. Increased compensation is also not a consequence and would no t be the response to a rule violation. Criminal charges can occur when a rule violation cr osses the line into illegality, but they are not a common consequence. Rather, they happen in rare, extreme cases. SOURCE: PD:251 SOURCE: LAP- PD-251\u2014Know the Code (Following Rules of Conduct)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q77", "number": 77, "question": "Which area of promotion will pricing affect?", "options": ["Choice of transportation channels", "Advertising budget", "Where the product is offered", "Materials used in production"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Advertising budget. Companies that sell low-priced items will not have as large an ad vertising budget as companies with higher priced items. Place decisions, including consideration of transportation c hannels and market location, as well as product decisions, such as selection of production materials, ar e not areas of promotion. SOURCE: PI:001 SOURCE: LAP- PI-002\u2014The Price Is Right (Nature of Pricing)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q78", "number": 78, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a potential unethical pricing issue as it rela tes to social responsibility:", "options": ["A manufacturing company increases prices on certain items to cover expenses to add new pollution-control devices.", "A pharmaceutical company sells a common lifesaving drug at extremely high prices in speci fic geographical regions.", "A clothing retailer deeply discounts goods in an effort to reduce excess inventory from the previous selling season.", "An oil company substantially increases its gasoline prices when the workers at a lar ge refinery go on strike."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " A pharmaceutical company sells a common lifesaving drug at extremely high prices in specif ic geographical regions. Social responsibility is defined as the duty of business to contribute to the well- being of society. Because the drug is common and has the capacity to save lives, an unethical issue is possible if the drug is sold at prices so high that some people can afford the drug while others cannot, which might be considered price discrimination. An oil company that substantially increases its gasoline prices when the workers at a large refinery go on strike does not necessarily present an unethical iss ue since the refinery lacks human resources to supply enough of the product to meet demand. A manufacturing company that increases prices on certain items to cover expenses to add new pollution- control devices is acting in an ethical manner and employing social responsibili ty to the natural environment. A clothing retailer that deeply discounts goods in an effort to reduce excess inventory from the previous selling season is not conducting socially irresponsible activities . SOURCE: PI:015 SOURCE: Jiranek, J. (2017, February 20). Who watches the watchmen: The ethics of drug price inflation. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://pjb.mycpanel2.princeton.edu/wp/index.php/2017/02/20/who-watches- the-watchmen- the-ethics- of-drug-price-inflation/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q79", "number": 79, "question": "Most marketers cannot expect to maintain their profit rates unless they", "options": ["introduce new products from time to time.", "test-market new products.", "allow products to move through the product life cycle.", "form venture teams to assist with product/service management."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Introduce new products from time to time. A certain percent of all industry profits come from succ essful new products. Product/Service management lets the business know what funds will be needed for research, testing, modifying, and producing products. Inadequate product/service management can r esult in product/service mistakes that may cost the company a large sum of money. Marketers do not allow products to move through the product life cycle; products do that naturally. Venture teams are small groups composed of representatives from different areas of a company for the purpose of seeking new ventures, or opportunities, for the business. They are usually used by large businesses. Not all produc ts need to be test-marketed because it is costly, delays entry into the full market, may n ot give an accurat e picture of performance, provides no guarantee of actual success, and the idea may be stolen by competitors while it is being tested. SOURCE: PM:001 SOURCE: LAP- PM-017\u2014Rapping Up Products (Nature of Product/Service Management)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q80", "number": 80, "question": "One way that advances in technology help businesses keep existing products on the market and extend their life cycle is by", "options": ["minimizing inventory.", "improving performance.", "attracting attention.", "demonstrating creativity."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Improving performance. Advances in technology that have allowed for the development of new materials and operating techniques are helping businesses improve the performance of their products. By improving existing products, businesses are able to keep them on the market and extend their life cycl e. Businesses have found that it is usually less expensive to update existing products th an to develop entirely new products. Advances in technology are allowing businesses to do this. Advanc es in technology do not help businesses keep existing products on the market by minimizing inventory, attracting attention, or demonstrating creativity. SOURCE: PM:039 SOURCE: Create Capture Connect. (2014, January 31). 5 tips to extend the product life cycle. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from http://createcaptureconnect.com/product-creation/5- tips-extend-product-life-cycle/"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q81", "number": 81, "question": "What synectics technique compares a problem with something else that is unrelated?", "options": ["Arbitrary metaphors", "Discretionary comparisons", "Forced analogies", "Deliberate allegories"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Forced analogies. A forced analogy is a synectics technique that compares a problem with s omething totally unrelated. Arbitrary metaphors, discretionary comparisons, and deliberate allegorie s are not terms widely used to describe a synectics creative-thinking method. SOURCE: PM:127 SOURCE: LAP- PM-127\u2014Unleash Your Mind (Techniques for Generating Product Ideas)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q82", "number": 82, "question": "A restaurant wants to develop new menu items that will appeal to its customers. A server mentions that many customers have asked for gluten-free meals, so the restaurant decides to try out a few new gluten- free menu items. What method of idea generation did the restaurant use?", "options": ["Observation", "Brainstorming", "Customers", "Trend research"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Customers. Companies often rely on input and feedback from customers to generate new product ide as. In this example, the restaurant gets feedback from customers and decides to introduce new menu items based on that feedback. This is not an example of brainstorming, observation, or trend research. SOURCE: Clark, B., Basteri, C.G., Gassen, C., & Walker, M. (2014). Marketing dynamics (3rd ed.) [p. 314]. Tinley Park, IL: The Goodheart-Willcox Co."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q83", "number": 83, "question": "Why do businesses want to meet quality standards?", "options": ["To determine how much work must be done", "To reduce costs", "To decrease profit", "To examine how long it takes to get a job done"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " To reduce costs. Businesses want to meet quality standards to reduce costs. Managers have recogniz ed that if employees do their jobs right the first time, they can minimize costs. Time isn't was ted redoing work, and fewer products end up as scrap. Time standards relate to how long it takes to get a job done. Quantity standards specify how much work must be done. Managers use standards to increase , rather than decrease, profit. SOURCE: PM:019 SOURCE: LAP- PM-008\u2014Raise the Bar (Grades and Standards)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q84", "number": 84, "question": "During the first year that Rick owned his new car, the vehicle seemed to spend more time i n the repair shop than it did on the road. Rick contacted the auto manufacturer and demanded his money back because the car seemed to be defective, but the manufacturer refused. A member of the Better Business Bureau agreed to act as an impartial third party in the dispute. The BBB member studied the f acts of the case, determined that the car was indeed defective, and decided how much money the carmaker would be required to refund to Rick. This is an example of", "options": ["arbitration.", "arbitron.", "attrition.", "automation."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Arbitration. When two parties engage in a dispute that they are unlikely to resolve on their own, an impartial third party may step in. The impartial third party, called an arbitrator, hears both sides' arguments, studies the facts of the case, and then determines a remedy for the situation. This process is called arbitration. The Arbitron Ratings Company uses consumer-generated data to analy ze radio advertising. Attrition is a natural reduction in numbers of people due to death, retirement, job cha nges, etc. Automation is a production method in which machines do tasks automatically. SOURCE: PM:017 SOURCE: LAP- PM-007\u2014Protect and Serve (Consumer Protection)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q85", "number": 85, "question": "Inventory reduction, sales stimulation, and new-product introduction are reasons that many busi nesses use __________ techniques.", "options": ["capital-investment", "stock-turn", "dual-sponsorship", "product-bundling"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Product-bundling. Product bundling is the practice of putting together a number of goods /services to create a one-price package. Bundled products are priced so that the consumer pays less for the bundl ed products than they would pay for products if the consumer purchased each product individually. The advantages to businesses that bundle products include inventory reduction for slow-movin g goods, sales increases, and lower new product-introduction costs. Stock-turn, dual-sponsorships, and capit al- investment are not techniques that provide businesses with the described advantages . SOURCE: PM:041 SOURCE: Lloyd, C.S. (2016, April 18). Advantages of product bundle sales. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.homecaremag.com/operations-marketing/april-2016/advantages- product-bundle-sales"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q86", "number": 86, "question": "Coca-Cola, General Mills, and Pillsbury are examples of __________ brands.", "options": ["generic", "national", "private", "unprotected"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " National. National brands are those for which the manufacturer assumes all the responsibility of branding. They are also called manufacturers' brands. Private brands are owned by middlemen. Generics are unbranded items that are plainly packaged, have standard or lower quality, are sold at lower prices than branded products, and receive little or no promotion. All of the brands listed are protected by trademark laws. SOURCE: PM:021 SOURCE: LAP- PM-006\u2014It's a Brand, Brand, Brand World! (Nature of Product Branding)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q87", "number": 87, "question": "A department store sells clothing from brands like Levi's, but it also sells its own private br ands of clothing, also known as __________ brands.", "options": ["business", "corporate", "value", "distributor"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Distributor. Distributor brands are owned by the retailer or wholesaler that sells the brands, rather than the manufacturer. Store brands and private brands are two types of distributor brands. Corporate brands are all the combined customer impressions and experiences associated with a particular company. V alue and business brands are not terms typically used to refer to distributor brands. SOURCE: PM:206 SOURCE: LAP- PM-020\u2014Corporate Identity (Nature of Corporate Branding)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q88", "number": 88, "question": "What concept is illustrated in the following situation: A new business uses newspape r publicity and personal selling to attract customers and plans a special sales event to generate publici ty for its grand opening.", "options": ["Advertising media", "Institutional promotion", "Product promotion", "Promotion"], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Promotion. Promotion is communicating information about goods, services, images, and/or ideas to achieve a desired outcome. The four basic types of promotion are advertising, sales promotion, perso nal selling, and publicity. Product promotion is used to convince customers to buy certain products . Institutional promotion is used to create a favorable image for a business. Advertising media are the agencies, means, or instruments used to convey messages. SOURCE: PR:001 SOURCE: LAP- PR-002\u2014Razzle Dazzle (Nature of Promotion)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q89", "number": 89, "question": "Coca-Cola's \"Always the real thing\" campaign is an example of what type of promotion?", "options": ["Taste", "Company", "Product", "Service"], "correct_index": 2, "correct_letter": "C", "explanation": " Product. Product promotion aims to persuade consumers to buy a good or service. Coca-Cola is promoting its soft drink. Coca-Cola is not promoting the specific company. Service and taste are not types of promotion. SOURCE: PR:002 SOURCE: LAP- PR-004\u2014Know Your Options (Product and Institutional Promotion)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q90", "number": 90, "question": "Which of the following examples depicts an advantage of using digital advertising:", "options": ["Viewers must interact with a video ad before continuing to a website.", "Ethan uses ad-blocking software so he can stream videos commercial-free.", "Conversion rates of banner ads are more difficult to measure than in print.", "Digital ads are more expensive than television advertisements."], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Viewers must interact with a video ad before continuing to a website. One of the biggest challenges facing any advertisement is engagement \u2014keeping the viewers' attention and making sure they are receiving the message. It is easy for viewers to ignore video ads, either digital or traditional, but if they are forced to interact with the ad in some way, they are more likely to pay attention to the ad and tak e in its message. Ad-blocking software is a disadvantage to digital advertising, rather than an ad vantage. Conversion rates are easier to measure online than in print. Finally, digital ads are generally cheaper than television advertisements. SOURCE: PR:100 SOURCE: Kurtz, D. (2013). Contemporary marketing: 2013 edition (pp. 516, 534). Mason, OH: South- Western, Cengage Learning."}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q91", "number": 91, "question": "Which of the following statements is true regarding the regulation of promotional activiti es:", "options": ["International laws make it difficult for consumers to sue large companies for unfair advertising practices.", "The regulation of promotional activities applies only to television, radio, and newspap er venues.", "Consumer groups have very little influence with the government regarding advertising legislatio n.", "Governmental restrictions in regard to promotional activities vary by country."], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " Governmental restrictions in regard to promotional activities vary by country. Because each government is structured differently, regulation varies from country to country. Consumer advocate groups are organizations that work to influence industry and government policies on behalf of the consumer. Consumer advocate groups often influence government regulation and policies. Because laws vary by country, it would be difficult to develop and fully enforce international laws regarding u nfair advertising practices. The ability to sue a company is dependent on the individual country's la ws and policies. Many promotional activities are subject to regulation, including media venues (television, radio, print); telemarketing; contests; and sweepstakes. SOURCE: PR:101 SOURCE: Wakeman, O. (2016, October 26). What is considered illegal marketing in other countries? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/considered-illegal- marketing- other -countries-73863.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q92", "number": 92, "question": "Which advertising medium offers the advantage of locating the promotional message near the poi nt of purchase?", "options": ["Newspapers", "Billboards", "Television", "Direct mail"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Billboards. Billboards are a form of outdoor media. They are often located on the business's proper ty or quite close to it. Other advantages of outdoor media include their ability to reach peop le who are on the move, low cost per exposure, high repeat exposure, and flexibility. Television, newspaper s, and direct mail can provide consumers with the same promotional message, but the message may be seen or heard at some distance from the business that is being promoted. SOURCE: PR:007 SOURCE: LAP- PR-003\u2014Ad-Quipping Your Business (Types of Advertising Media)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q93", "number": 93, "question": "What does a business's customers recommending the business to their friends exemplify?", "options": ["Word- of-mouth communication", "Providing a testimonial", "Verbal assertiveness", "One- on-one selling"], "correct_index": 0, "correct_letter": "A", "explanation": " Word- of-mouth communication. This is promotion and publicity for a business provided by custom ers who tell others of their satisfaction with the business. Therefore, customers recommending the busines s to their friends is an example of word- of-mouth communication. In many cases, these recommendations lead to additional sales because people tend to believe their friends and take their advice. A testimonial is a statement by an identified user of a product proclaiming the benefits received from the use of the product. Verbal assertiveness is a confident attitude that involves the use of words. Recommending a business to friends is not an example of one- on-one selling. SOURCE: PR:247 SOURCE: Mosley, M. (2017, June 25). Why is word of mouth marketing so important? Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.socialmediatoday.com/marketing/why-word-mouth- marketing- so-important"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q94", "number": 94, "question": "An important public relations activity in business involves giving public relation s advice to", "options": ["the media.", "management.", "government.", "the public."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Management. Some businesses maintain a public relations department while others use the s ervices of a public relations agency. One of the functions of the department or agency is to advise m anagement on public relations issues, such as taking a position on public issues or preparing b usiness employees to make public appearances. Giving advice is a public relations activity intended to help management make the best decisions regarding the business's relations with the public. An importan t public relations activity in business does not involve giving public relations advice to the media, the gov ernment, or the public. SOURCE: PR:252 SOURCE: Inc. (2018, May 5). Public relations . Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://www.inc.com/encyclopedia/public-relations.html"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q95", "number": 95, "question": "Which of the following is an internal factor that affects a business's selling policies:", "options": ["Primary competitors", "Financial resources", "Customers' wants", "Government regulations"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Financial resources. Selling policies are the guidelines for selling activities that inv olve interaction with customers or potential customers. Many factors affect how a business structures its selling polici es. An internal factor that affects a business's selling policies is its financial resources \u2014the sources of money (e.g., sales, dividends) a business has. Generally, the more money that a business has , the more flexible it can be with its selling policies. For example, a business that has access to a lot of m oney can buy more inventory, take advantage of bulk discounts, and pass the savings on to the customer. Having sufficient financial resources often allows the business to extend credit options to customers. Competitors , customers' wants, and government regulations are external factors that affect a business's selling policies. SOURCE: SE:932 SOURCE: LAP- SE-121\u2014Sell Right (Selling Policies)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q96", "number": 96, "question": "Which of the following is a reason why the ethical and legal issues involved in se lling activities are extremely important:", "options": ["Sellers must understand how to criticize competitors.", "Buyers avoid doing business with unethical salespeople.", "Sales staff must know when they can legally bend the truth.", "Sales managers are not responsible for what the sales staff does."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Buyers avoid doing business with unethical salespeople. Unethical salespeople often lose c ustomers and create a negative image of their company. Making erroneous statements about competitors or bending the truth to make a sale are typical examples of unethical sales practices. Sales managers must monitor the practices of their sales staff because they are ultimately responsible for the actions a nd claims of their staff. SOURCE: SE:106 SOURCE: LAP- SE-129\u2014Keep It Real \u2014In Sales (Legal and Ethical Considerations in Selling)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q97", "number": 97, "question": "What information could a salesperson obtain by examining a product?", "options": ["Care", "Texture", "Value", "Price"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Texture. A lot of information is found by examining the product itself. A salesperson can determine a product's texture by holding and touching the item. Through careful examination and observation, a salesperson should be able to acquire product knowledge about any item. Information about price, c are, and value cannot always be obtained by examining a product. SOURCE: SE:062 SOURCE: LAP- SE-131\u2014Get Informed (Acquiring Product Information for Use in Selling)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q98", "number": 98, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a salesperson describing a product's construction and materials:", "options": ["\"Many of my customers have owned and used this product for more than 10 years.\"", "\u201cTo accommodate your d\u00e9cor, this product is available in a variety of finishes and colors.\u201d", "\u201cAnother feature about this item is that it can also be used in several ways.\u201d", "\"Because the manufacturer uses hi gh-grade materials to produce this item, its quality is superior.\""], "correct_index": 3, "correct_letter": "D", "explanation": " \"Because the manufacturer uses high-grade materials to produce this item, its quality is superior.\" T o influence the customer's buying decision, the salesperson must describe the product features and benefits to the customer. One feature that the salesperson might describe is the product's constructi on. This involves telling the customer about the materials and processes used to make the product. This technique is often used to emphasize the product's high quality. A salesperson describi ng the product' s finishes and colors is pointing out features about appearance and style. If a customer can use the product in many ways, the salesperson is emphasizing the product's uses. Pointing out the length of tim e that past customers have owned and used the product is emphasizing the item's durability. SOURCE: SE:109 SOURCE: LAP- SE-113\u2014Find Features, Boost Benefits (Feature-Benefit Selling)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q99", "number": 99, "question": "After Dana helped her customer select a sweater, she asked her how she would like to pay for it. This is an example of what phase of the selling process?", "options": ["Establishing relationships with customers", "Reaching closure", "Discovering client needs", "Prescribing solutions to needs"], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Reaching closure. Reaching closure involves identifying customer objections and completing the transaction. In this case, Dana is closing the sale by discussing the transaction. Di scovering client needs involves asking the customer questions in order to determine what they are looking for. Establis hing relationships involves the initial contact the salesperson has with the customer. Pres cribing solutions to needs involves the salesperson offering solutions to satisfy the customers' needs. SOURCE: SE:048 SOURCE: LAP- SE-048\u2014Set Your Sales (The Selling Process)"}, {"id": "u-26c361ff-q100", "number": 100, "question": "When assessing risks associated with an upcoming event, sport/event organizations shoul d acquire input from all levels of management and", "options": ["public relations agencies.", "vertical staff members.", "financial consultants.", "local personnel inspectors."], "correct_index": 1, "correct_letter": "B", "explanation": " Vertical staff members. Vertical staff members refers to all employees who are not in man agement. Ticket takers, security guards, guest relations representatives, and merchandise sales perso nnel are examples of employees who might provide insight when conducting risk assessment. For example, sales personnel can provide information regarding shoplifting and its risks. By gathering as m uch information as possible from staff members, sport/event organizations can conduct comprehensive risk ass essments in many areas and develop appropriate procedures to handle each situation or issue. Publi c relations agencies are hired by a business to develop and manage public relations activities f or the business. Financial consultants are hired by a business to manage the business's financial matters. L ocal personnel inspector is not a term widely used by sport/event organizations. SOURCE: SM:076 SOURCE: Fit for Work. (2017, March 13). Risk assessment. Retrieved September 10, 2018, from https://fitforwork.org/blog/risk-assessment/"}], "question_count": 100}}, "missed": {}}